Hey, how's it going?
There we go.
The ritual has been completed.
How's everybody doing, huh?
It's Sunday.
Good afternoon, good evening, good night.
Wherever you are.
The Coke Zero.
Hey, the oplia.
How you doing?
It goes better now that the can is opened?
Exactly.
It's always better after the can is opened.
That sound itself, I think I've been Pavlovian-ly triggered or conditioned to always get a happy feeling when I hear that sound.
It's weird how that works.
Hey, Smelly Ellie.
How's it going?
Hey Oliver, first time catching alive.
Just made some banana bread.
So having a great Sunday so far.
I hope you are too.
Dude, banana bread is the best.
I have a co-worker who makes amazing banana bread, brings it to work occasionally.
And I'm not afraid to admit that I eat copious amounts of it every time.
One of the best things ever, banana bread.
Enjoy it, Smelly Ellie.
Hey Matt.
Just Matt.
Hyped for more neuter cooking.
Definitely we're gonna be cooking today.
But come on, let's not get our hopes up too much here.
I mean things went almost a little bit too well last time.
So honestly I'm prepared to drop everything.
I'm prepared to die to the first thing I'm seeing and that's okay.
I'm not gonna have any expectations, you know.
It went so well that it scares me a little bit now.
But we'll have to see.
You're right, it doesn't account for good morning.
But what if I intentionally meant for you not to have a good morning, but to have a good afternoon, evening and night?
Hmm?
Think about that one.
Have I had banana bread?
Have you had banana cake?
It's similar, it's just a little more healthy even though you can't really say it's healthy.
It's amazing.
Instant noodles with chicken.
Wait, so you make instant noodles and then you add some chicken yourself after?
That sounds pretty dope, if that's the case.
Your banana bread is great too, Oliver.
Thanks Diego!
Thank you.
I mean I try, I mean I can't make it anymore because I don't really have an air fryer broke.
I fucked it up.
RIP.
I gotta go bury it somewhere in a field.
No, it's a cooking stream, definitely.
I'm gonna try my best.
Well, it's morning for me so now I'm scared.
Oh, I'm kidding!
Good morning, good afternoon, good evening, good night.
Let's just change it to that.
Yeah, RIP to the air fryer.
So I was trying to make some, so I bought some ready-made food that only had to be heated, right?
And I read the instructions and it said you could heat it in the oven or the air fryer or whatever, you know?
And there were specific instructions for the air fryer.
And it's one of those things with plastic on top that you punch holes in.
And I was already a little bit, you know, not quite sure about that.
Putting plastic in there in an air fryer?
Hmm, you know, doesn't sound good, but the instructions say to do it.
So I fucking do it.
And what do you know?
It didn't go well.
I should have listened to my intuition.
Fucking plastic blew up into the heating elements and now there's plastic stuck to everything in there.
It wasn't meant to be made in the microwave, unfortunately.
I don't think it's good.
Yeah, I will... from now on I'm gonna use my own intuition and logic, man.
Like, what kind of shitty instructions are those?
It's okay, though.
Maybe I can repair it by scraping off all the plastic, but I think it's gonna be a tough one.
Or I can... maybe I can get the heating elements replaced.
I don't know.
Yeah, it sucks.
It was a good soldier, though.
It has been frying the air for me for a long while.
I shall assume you misread the instructions.
It's possible.
I mean, it is possible.
I don't have the instructions anymore, but it is definitely possible that I misread.
I don't think I did, though.
Anyway, so the plan for today... obviously we're gonna be playing Noiter.
Let me... oh no.
By the way, I figured out what's making that sound.
So check this out.
I'm using a program called Special K so that I can launch Noiter in a mode where I'm able to minimize the game without the game pausing.
Because if I have to switch to the overlay with the map drawing, it would be kind of annoying to have the game pause all the time, basically.
Right?
But I think whenever the game crashes via launching it with this thing, it has a built-in sound effect that plays that.
And for some reason, it crashes in the beginning?
It did this last time, too.
I don't understand what's going on.
It's weird.
Yeah, Special K, like the Kellogg's.
Yeah.
Okay, hold on.
Let me see.
Does it work now?
Okay, we don't we don't get a crashing sound.
Good.
Whoops, that's way too zoomed in.
So I did some stuff last time.
I figured out a bunch of things.
I brought the tablet to the to the lake house.
And we opened a portal to one of the underground enclosures of what have you.
And we found some colorful stuff in there.
I'm sure it has other uses, but we did that.
I am currently in the ancient laboratory.
So I'm doing this one right now.
That one.
Also, let me change the size of this.
That seems better.
Yep.
Then we have the demon eye that produces platforms.
I need to explore that shit, as it says here.
That's on my to-do list.
This one, actually, we did.
We explored the dark area west of hemisphere.
And I am tempted to fill that part out on the map.
The only issue is... I would have to go back and sort of... because it was kind of a complicated cave.
But I kind of want to map it out, you know?
But I'm not sure if that cave is always the same or if it changes.
So I don't want to make it.
Well, I guess I could make the outline of it.
Yeah, I'm gonna make the outline of it, I guess.
And then for some reason, I wrote get polymorphine and bring it to stone west of lake.
Honestly, guys, I have no idea what I meant with that.
But I will...
I'm gonna try and go to the west of lake and see what stone there is.
I must have had some kind of theory.
So yeah, we're gonna be doing that as well.
Eat more shrooms?
Kind of want to do that as well.
I want to experiment more with that.
We... apparently we turned all the lava into poison or something.
And that's kind of insane.
Because the entire lava lake is now gone.
It completely evaporated.
So yeah, this is what we've been working with.
We are currently somewhere... wait, we are like... actually, we're about here.
Oh, I wrote dark area here.
So we're about here somewhere.
Because we went to the west of dark area.
So that is actually the location of... I was about to say the ancient labyrinth.
But no, the ancient laboratory is where we are right now.
And I'm gonna explore that today.
Then we filled this out last time.
The way it connects snowy depths to the hemisphere.
And you know what's cool about this?
I actually have a map of some sort now, you know?
I can sort of... let's say I were to dig from here all the way through here to there.
Would I actually arrive in the coal pits?
Based on my layout here?
I think I would, you know?
That's one of the things we can sort of test down the road.
But yeah, I am prepared to lose everything.
We did so well last time.
It could only go downhill from here, I'm sure.
Anyway, hopefully all that came across nicely on stream.
Alright, hopefully we won't get a crash.
Alright, I'm gonna close you guys down.
I'm sorry guys.
I will now play the game.
Hold on.
Click there.
Oh, also I need to turn off the sound effects.
There we go.
Good luck.
Maybe I'll check in at some point soon.
I intend to play this a lot today.
I actually am not... so I actually just came over or got over a little bit of a sickness that I had Thursday to Friday and some of yesterday.
I actually wanted to stream on Friday because Friday, right?
And that was a perfect day for streaming, but I didn't feel very good.
So I've been looking forward to this, dude.
What was I doing?
Let me actually take stock of what I have.
I have this weird wand.
Triplicate bolt.
Nice.
And teleport wand and I had the digging wand and then I have the healing that is empty.
Okay.
Then I have... what is this?
The worm blood.
That's right.
We figured that out too.
If you drink this, you get night vision.
A big fucking deal.
Think about it.
We can also use this in the other dark area somewhere down below.
I forgot where it is, but you remember the place with the... I want to say like a pyramid stacked on top of an inverted pyramid type of structure where something was inside.
I kind of forgot what was inside there, but we got to go there as well at some point and map that out too.
We have to map out everything.
Hmm.
Then we have all these spells.
Okay.
Concentrated mana, huh?
Sure.
Concentrate me.
What are we gonna find?
I need to get back into this.
Let me just quickly, you know, get the movement into my body here.
Okay.
We have 270 HP.
Nice.
There's an enemy down there.
Oh, I remember now we had a... this wand is not that great.
This was the only thing that was kind of shitty about this run so far.
We don't do a lot of damage.
Hello.
Oh, no, wait.
He's blocking everything.
I remember this.
Some of them blocked a lot, but it was only like randomly.
Oh, nice.
Okay.
That wasn't too bad.
What's that?
Oh, teleportation.
Kind of don't want to touch that.
Wait, what did that guy... Oh, he teleported, of course.
He was in the teleportation.
I really love that the rules that apply to me also applies to my enemies.
You know?
Pretty cool.
What happens if the enemies go into these lasers?
Oh, that guy teleported again.
He's over here now.
You know what?
I'm gonna take care of him because he will fuck me up later, probably, if I don't.
Oh, no.
He disappeared again.
This bastard.
Oh, and then I had this perk.
Hungry ghost, which seems kind of useless.
I'm actually so sad I took that.
I should have been more patient and done another re-roll.
I mean, I haven't noticed what it does, you know?
Maybe it actually does help me, but I have my doubts.
I have yet to be proven wrong on that.
And it makes this kind of annoying sound when it moves.
Listen now.
You hear it?
It's like a mechanical sound.
A little bit annoying.
Damn!
He got fucked up.
Oh, oh, I have this awesome shield as well.
This shield is actually amazing.
One of the best perks.
Where are we now?
Are we still in the ancient laboratory?
What's that?
Pheromone.
Wait, what is happening here?
Why is everything exploding?
What's that?
What the hell is that?
Rock.
Hmm.
All right.
Cool.
I have to remember, I do have my laser that I can use to dig with if I need to.
What's that up there?
On.
Wait, what did it say?
Oh, unstable polymorphine.
That's bad.
I mean, it's kind of fun.
I actually kind of like unstable polymorphine.
Unstable.
No, wait.
I didn't mean that.
I meant unstable teleportation.
That's what I like.
Like this one.
I kind of want to keep the eye.
Maybe I don't want this book on me.
Let me see here.
Here, I'm safe.
I am safe.
My research with real under.
Right.
I had this theory about real understanding.
And every time you pick up one of those orbs, you get like, you gain true knowledge.
So there's something going on there.
There's a connection for sure.
This is polymorphine.
Don't want that.
That's what's doing that.
Okay.
Why is there so much polymorphine here?
Hey, man.
His shots are completely being absorbed by my shield.
Or deflected, I should say.
This is weird.
Uh, hello.
Huh?
It's me.
Wait, what?
Try to kick me.
What the hell?
I can't hit him.
Wow.
Nothing hits him.
Wait, what?
Hey, come here.
Uh, no.
Wait, are they gonna kill him?
Hey, he's killing them for me.
He's kicking them.
What is happening?
He kicked them into the unstable polymorphine.
He does 11 damage.
Is that like my alter ego?
What is happening?
He actually killed him.
Wait, is he my friend?
My dude.
Wait, are you gonna... He doesn't seem... Are you gonna...
Oh, motherfucker.
Okay, so he's not my friend, but he's also not my enemy.
I can't really hurt him, it seems.
Wait, unless I kick him.
Jesus.
Okay, okay.
I'm not gonna mess with you.
I don't know what to do about this.
I'm kind of a...
I'm not sure what to do here.
Maybe I'll just ignore him for now.
I mean, he's kind of slow.
It's okay, I think.
And he does kind of fuck up the enemies.
Whoa.
I wonder what this... Oh, yeah, right.
So...
Oh, wait a minute.
So, does triangle pyramid sign mean fire?
Is that what that means?
Because he does fire.
I remember last time we saw one of these that did electricity.
Dude, you have so much HP.
And I do very little damage also.
Let's not forget that part.
I'm completely slimed up right now.
What's that?
Pheromone?
Also pheromone?
Whoa!
What's up, man?
Wait, I can make them my friends.
Put them in pheromone.
Hold on, I have an idea.
Let's drink worm blood.
Can I see anything special?
Kind of want to experiment with that more.
I think it's more than just... See, he's my friend.
He's my friend now, look.
Hello.
Uh...
What?
Wait.
Okay, you know what?
I'm gonna kill him.
I don't trust this.
Dude, I just realized pheromone is actually insane.
If you put pheromone on someone, they're just gonna stand there and you can hit them.
No issue.
It's like broken almost.
Also, my colors are completely fucked because of this worm blood.
Hello.
Oh, he's blocking.
He has that effect on him.
What's that?
Kivaskivi.
This is so bright.
Oh wait, I don't have any... You know what?
Maybe I'll get rid of the book.
Yeah, fuck the book for now.
Give me this.
There's gotta be something about this, right?
Like, we gotta be able to do something with that.
I mean, we've seen it for the longest time.
So many times, but I haven't been able to figure out what's going on.
Can we get rid of this light?
Wait, what's happening?
Neutral.
Projectile spells your cash short circuit?
I've never seen that.
What the hell?
That's a nasty debuff.
Wow.
I had to use all of my mana there to kill him.
Well, sir, do you like Kivaskivis?
He's on fire now.
What's that?
Damage?
Wait, damage boost?
I just had a damage boost effect on me.
What the hell?
No idea where that came from.
Could I be going over here?
Hold on.
One, two, three, go.
Wait, where am I now?
Okay, I've not been here.
That guy does some kind of frost stuff.
Look at his clothes.
They're all like frosty.
Icy.
Oh, oh my God.
Is he shotgunning me?
Holy shit.
He got polymorph into something and then I killed him.
Okay, we're back here now.
This way, that way.
Here, here.
Let me go up here.
Oh, we got a dude there.
Kind of want to get in there and see what's going on.
I can do it.
Man, I love this plasma.
I've gotten better at using it, too.
I'm not damaging myself all the time.
All right, show yourself.
Love these little entrances here where you can just go nuts on them.
What is this again?
Pheromone, right?
Why will it not tell me what it is?
I hate that.
It's not very precise with the mouth.
Oh, it is pheromone.
Okay.
Pheromone.
So that guy does.
I want to say frost because I don't recognize the symbol.
Thank you.
Let's see what he does.
Yep, that's frost.
So the square with lines on the side is frost.
Like ice, whatever.
Oh, okay.
Wait, did I just block that?
Unless that was because there was a bit of explosion there.
I do block explosion.
Nice.
Whoa.
I am debating whether or not I should go back and heal somehow.
Because I have refreshers.
The last time I was in this position with half HP, I decided to move on and then I died when I had the opportunity to heal.
I feel like I should go heal.
Hold on.
What's happening in here?
Hey, how's it going?
What's this?
Pheromone.
Hey.
Oh, no, no, no, didn't mean to do that.
Okay.
Wait, what's that?
Wait, did he just respawn?
Wow.
Okay.
So it looks like when you kill them, they become a little orb.
And if you don't kill the orb, they will respawn.
And when I kill them... Oh, berserkium.
Nice.
I like me some of that.
More of it.
Man, I wish I had more bottles.
There's the dude again.
Maybe with berserkium, I can kill him.
I cannot.
That guy is insanely robust.
Don't want to aggro him.
Or do I?
I kind of want to go that way.
Let's see it.
Maybe if I walk too far, he's not going to follow me.
Whoa.
Oh, wait, that was a bit risky what I just did.
Oh, he... he... he polymorphed into something.
Maybe if that guy hits polymorphine.
Sir?
Oh, wait, I probably can't.
How do I... Hmm.
If I can turn him into something else, then I can kill him.
Then again, he does sort of help me in a weird way, too.
Nice.
Okay, I think I should try and find some healing.
Uh, hmm.
Let me think.
Where do we have healing?
I mean, I could go back down and find one of the refresh, because I have some left.
I think I may do it.
It sounds a little pussy, but honestly, I think that's what it takes.
I'm going to go back.
I'm doing the safe thing here.
And while I go back, I will explore a couple more areas on the way, maybe.
Unstable teleportation.
I don't need that.
Hold on, what's going on here?
I should not be teleporting into unknown areas.
It seems like a bad idea in general.
What's this?
Teleportation and pheromone.
I feel like pheromone is insane.
I should be collecting that in some bottle if I find one.
Actually, I did find a bottle just before.
I could empty that and use it, but I'm gonna move on here.
I think this is where, yeah, this is where I entered.
This is the dark area.
And I still have some left.
Okay, check this out.
You can't see anything now.
Night vision.
Oh, hello!
There's a guy in there.
He was hiding in the dark!
That bastard!
Oh my god, will you die already?
Thank you.
Why are they bleeding so much sand?
And look, now we're back.
Isn't that cool?
Kind of want to get more, uh, warm blood.
That is like an insanely nice thing to have in this game.
So the question is, where exactly do I have a refresh?
Oh, it's right here.
Perfect!
I thought it was further down.
Nice!
And now we can heal.
In fact, I'm gonna do it.
Or should I wait just a bit more?
No, wait, it only is like half of my HP, no?
Let me see.
Yeah, okay, nice.
375.
That's actually sick.
You know, another thing I want to do, I want to go back through all these areas here, like even the coal pits and all that, because there's bound to be more hearts, right, that I missed, because I had to go through them quite quickly last time, or the first time I went through them.
Because I had such a bad time, you know, I was almost dying all the time.
So, but why is this...
What's going on with the electricity there?
Also, do I want to... Hold on, I had some stuff here that I wanted to try.
Now that I'm here, I can actually edit my wand, right?
Homing could be cool.
Maybe I want to try to find some kind of weapon that can kill that thing that blocked everything.
I guess... Hmm.
This one is actually kind of sick.
This just gives me lower castellae.
How is this not just a positive?
Rainbow Glimmer is actually sick.
Like, it costs no mana.
It's a free castellae decrease.
Why, why would I not just put that here?
Hold on.
Let me, let me try something.
So, let's see how fast this is now.
Wait, I'm not actually sure.
Wait, what, what the...
Okay, I'm not actually quite sure what's going on here.
The effect is completely gone, like, of this spell.
Oh, never mind.
It's...
Okay.
I don't think it did anything, because I already had the castellae so low that this effectively does nothing here.
You know, it's the exact same... Yeah, you can also hear it.
It's the same speed.
Okay.
Um, let's see.
Oh, I had the plasma beam enhancer.
But for some reason, I really wanted this to work on that, and it didn't.
Oh my god, guys.
It's a shuffle wand.
It, it does work.
Oh my god, dude.
Wait a minute.
It does work.
10 mana?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Maybe I put this on here, then?
Oh, that's super slow, though.
Isn't it?
That's way too slow.
It adds... So recharge time is very high on this.
Do I have anything that reduces recharge time?
I mean, this reduces castellae, but that's not what I'm looking for.
This one reduces recharge time.
Wait a minute.
If I remove this from that, let me just quickly test.
Wait, what?
Wait a fucking minute.
What?
Wait a minute, is this shooting faster now?
Look how fast my mana's gone.
What?
Okay, I don't understand this at all.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
This, it's way better without that.
I don't understand this game.
I don't understand what's going on.
So hold on, we have modifier here.
Oh wait, I have reduced recharge.
If I remove that...
Now it's super slow.
If I remove both of these, it's insanely slow.
Okay, let's try and understand this.
So right now, there's a modifier on it, reduces spread.
Cool.
Speed up, cool.
Double spell.
Which means it's going to cast this one and the next, but there is no next.
So it's going to go like, what is the next?
It's this one.
Right?
What is the... so the recharge time is 0.58.
This one, okay, so recharge time is 0.58.
And that's it.
Castelay is already extremely small.
So what we're seeing here between shots is the recharge time.
You can also see that in the top right, right?
With the recharge bar.
So okay, that makes sense.
Now we add this, reduces recharge time and reduces castelay, but that doesn't really matter because castelay is not the bottleneck here.
So it's going to be faster.
You know, you see the recharge bar up here moves faster, right?
That makes sense.
Now we add one more.
And now we have reduced to 0.66 in total, which means we are actually below zero.
So it's like instant, basically.
That's why it's so fast.
But why does adding this make it slower?
This reduces recharge time.
Oh, wait a minute.
This is a projectile.
So this casts... Wait a minute.
If I were to do this...
Okay, that's the exact same.
Never mind.
Okay, then I don't understand.
I don't get it.
Is it the...
Okay, the only thing that makes... No, I don't understand.
The only thing this one does is to reduce recharge time, which should be beneficial.
Okay, I don't know.
Honestly, I don't fucking understand that.
Whatever.
This is clearly better.
The only issue is that we run low on mana now, you know?
So if we can put this on a wand...
Let's see.
If we can put this on a wand with much more mana...
Oh, I don't really have that great wands.
Like, hold on.
Didn't I have a sick wand at some point?
Where was that wand?
I had a wand at some point somewhere.
That wasn't too... Is there a wand right here?
Wait a minute.
Small teleport.
Where?
There.
I see something on the floor here.
I think that's a wand we have there.
That one.
Oh, that's the one that's doing... Okay, never mind.
I thought there was a wand there.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, it's a lamp.
Never mind.
I thought that was a wand.
I'm starting to see wands everywhere for some reason.
Okay, we got to be on the lookout for a wand that is better, so we can actually sustain this.
Or we find add mana.
That would be insane-o style.
Yeah, that's the plan.
This goes there, then we have the healing.
I'll actually change these two.
Okay, so if I add the chainsaw here, that should make that much faster.
Right?
Okay, my brain is broken.
I'm sorry.
The chainsaw also makes this slower now, too!
Wait, what if I add this here at the end?
Okay, oh, oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, hold on now.
That's interesting.
What?
Wait, wait a minute.
Is that even faster now?
What the fuck?
Like, look at the difference.
That is very weird.
What if we put a triple there?
Wow.
So it's shooting...
It's just doing the same thing again and again and again, but we reduced everything down to zero, so it's like brrrr.
You know?
It's actually a sick wand.
Like, 790 mana max and mana charge speed of 261.
That is... dope.
Right?
Isn't that insane?
Hold on.
So with this speed right now, how much damage are we talking?
Oh wait, I can't test that there.
This has become a good wand, I think.
225?
Yo.
Like, 200 ish damage.
That's pretty dope.
I like it.
So, but wait a minute.
Wait, is that... hold on.
Yeah, I don't need the chainsaw there.
Oh, oh, wait a minute.
If we put a double here...
and we shoot both of these at the same time...
No, put this here.
Like that.
I mean, it's still nice.
It's not bad, you know?
It's pretty dope.
Yeah, I think it's about the same.
No, actually it's a little faster.
A little faster.
With the chainsaw.
Yep, I like it.
I like it.
I like it a lot.
Nice.
What else should I be bringing?
Maybe I'll try, because we have some slots here we can use now.
Now that we got rid of the chainsaw, maybe we can make some fun happen.
Let me test some things.
Let's get rid of that and try this.
Okay.
That's... I go way too fast on that, and I do no damage at all.
Look at that.
I mean, it shoots so fast.
Fast, boy!
But it's just like a oomph so quick.
What else could I... oh, wait a minute.
Cat... oh, wait, oh, wait, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Oh, but wait, I'm not limited by cast a lay here.
This recharge time is the main thing, so fuck that.
Okay, but that's still fine.
This one is done for now.
Then we have this one up here.
What about concentrated light?
Let me try that again.
Okay, that's fast.
130.
It's not as much damage as I would like.
How about... yeah, I don't really have any other spells.
I'm kind of short on spells.
Yeah.
No, we're going back to the triplicate bolt.
That one's definitely the best I have.
Okay.
I could... oh, you know what?
I could try something.
What is causing me a lot of mana in this rotation?
That one is 25, so it's obvious... so both of these cost a lot of mana, too.
If I get rid of that...
Wait a minute.
Is that... is that even faster?
No, it's not faster than before, of course, but...
And what I mean is faster than the one I had when I started this dream.
Maybe.
Maybe speed up is not necessary.
And then we add this.
How much mana does that cost?
Like, over time?
It's negligible, I would say.
I... um... I think I like the fast version more, both of these, without that.
This is like a shotgun, basically.
It's a... it's a long shotgun shell.
Like, it's shot.
Bam.
Right on target.
I could make it glimmer, I guess, but I don't want to do that.
Hmm... oh, you know what?
Maybe I... that faster?
It's about the same, I think.
All right, I think we're good here.
I just wanted to heal.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Good thing I already made a path somewhere.
Where was my path?
Wait, where was my path?
Did I take over here?
Wait, where did I... how did I get up here?
Didn't I... am I losing my mind?
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I went up along the... along the lava stuff.
So we're gonna have to dig.
We're gonna have to dig.
I remember now.
Wait, is that less powerful now?
Call me crazy, but this one was digging way better last time.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Why is this so bad now?
I'm losing my mind.
Well, okay, I don't get it.
And with the speed,
I think it's about equal here, because I kind of want to put this here now.
Is that gonna change?
No.
That's weird.
I just seem to remember this digging, like, way faster up.
Am I crazy?
Maybe not.
I mean, it's definitely... it has more... what do you call it?
It's more wide now than it was before.
This thing's like crap.
Also, am I getting... oh, shit.
Wait, whoa, whoa.
What?
Fire?
What's causing fire?
Is it the chainsaw?
Wait, hold on.
I'm not liking this.
Maybe it is the chainsaw that... no, wait.
Hmm.
Let me test something real quick.
I feel like there's a fire effect being added with this.
Am I crazy?
No, it's also here now.
Okay, that's weird.
All right.
Also, I need to fill my water bottle.
We use all our worm blood anyway, so let's just get that done.
And now we go.
Like, look how slow this is.
That's so weird.
Oh, wait a minute.
I can make a very narrow and then teleport through, of course.
I keep forgetting that I have that capability.
Except I really can't, because I need some space to teleport there.
Bro, what have I done to my wand?
Hold on a second.
There's something going on here.
I need to get to the bottom of it.
I think it's the wand itself.
Hold on.
I need to understand this.
I'm losing my mind.
Was it this wand that I had?
Let me see.
So if I go here and I... let me take like this.
I think it may have been that one that I had.
No, it wasn't a shuffle, wasn't it?
Yeah, yeah.
It was on a shuffle wand.
I remember that.
And I believe it was on this one, actually.
Because I remember the healing one was the long one.
Right?
Let me see this one.
There it is.
That's what I remember.
Now we're fucking cooking.
And you know what?
Maybe I don't mind having that being in here, even though it's a shuffle.
You know?
Sometimes I'm gonna get a wide one.
Sometimes I don't.
Whatever.
It's fine.
That's okay.
I like it.
Cool.
Done.
Done deal.
Finally.
I was losing my mind just now, but now I'm back.
I'm back, baby.
Oh, look at the speed on this.
Much better.
Doink.
And we're back.
Back to the ancient laboratory.
Just go west.
The cool thing is I can just refer to the map if I'm lost.
Oh, but wait.
I actually can't see shit in here now, but maybe I can go through... I sort of remember.
Shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I... no, I can't.
Nope.
This may be a bad idea.
Fuck.
I can't see anything.
Damn it.
Hold on.
How am I gonna... Okay.
You know what?
I know what to do.
Check this out.
We're gonna...
go up here.
Wait a minute.
We had another access path to it, didn't we?
Over here somewhere.
Wait, what was this?
No, no, no, no.
I'm thinking about the other place.
This was not the place.
I'm gonna... I'm gonna go grab a worm to get worm blood.
I'm doing it.
Don't care.
Whoop!
Is that one?
Wiggling egg.
Go!
And kill it.
Oh, there's two of them.
Wait, whoa!
Why are there so many worms?
Oh, it broke that egg too.
Oh, I see.
Should I be... hold on.
Water that.
Just eat a lot of this shit right now.
This should be more than enough.
And we have some in our bottle now.
Uh, then we go... then we quickly go over here.
Hooray.
Uh, west.
Go west.
Quick, quick, quick.
Oh, shit.
Wait, where is it?
I'm taking a very bad path here, I realize.
Oh, no!
Come on.
30 seconds.
Here we go, here we go.
Yeah.
Ah, yeah, I never would have made it through here.
No way.
Nice.
All right, we're back.
We are back, baby.
So I am maybe regretting that I did all this up here because it does go on quick.
You know?
I mean, it does more damage, but it's also less sustained damage, I would say.
So maybe I fucked up.
We'll have to see.
We'll have to see how it feels.
I don't even know what I'm looking for here.
I feel like I've explored everything already.
Like, it's just some kind of weird little side area type deal.
Ah, I'm going to dig my way through here.
Oh, look how effective that is.
Lovely.
Just lovely.
Oh, wait, there's actually stuff in here.
Why is that little pixel not being removed?
Pheromone, hmm.
Oh, come on, Pixel.
Okay.
Oh, hello, little frost man.
He has the armor buff on.
I hate to see that.
Damn, what is this place?
Wow, he's blocking everything.
Wow, dude.
Holy shit.
Okay, let's not fucking falter right now.
Focus up.
Yeah, I need to be way more precise with this wand.
Is that... if I miss a shot, I'm vulnerable for a long time.
What is that?
That is concentrated mana.
Oh, oh, shit, we got a boss here.
Uli alchemisti.
Alchemist?
Huh?
Where?
I'm scared.
I'm so scared right now.
Oh, is he up here?
No, wait, the health bar is gone.
Oh, what?
He's somewhere down here.
Below me?
What's that?
Teleportation?
Oh, oh, oh, shit.
Here we go.
Okay, we have a boss.
I'm gonna have an escape route ready in case shit hits the fan.
I'm gonna just go this way if shit hits the fan.
But let's see what we're dealing with.
Oh my god, he's small.
Abandoned alchemy.
Oh, wait, no, that's not him.
That's not him.
Oh, shit.
What the fuck?
Don't teleport.
Don't do this to me.
Get me out of this.
Come on.
I don't want to be this dude.
I don't want to be this man.
How long am I like this?
Okay, there we go.
Man, I actually don't like my new wand.
Okay, this is looking bad.
This guy looks insane.
What the fuck?
Hey.
Oh, and he has a shield too.
Oh, never mind.
He doesn't.
What?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, his shield is back.
Oh, it just comes back on randomly, it seems.
Damn, dude.
I'm gonna lure him back here.
Oh, yeah, that is... yeah, don't shoot the shield.
How's my HP?
Oh, we also have a heal.
We have to remember this.
Whoa!
Okay, wait for the shield to be off.
Blast him.
Damn!
I need to... I need to water myself.
Oh my god, we also have enemies here.
I don't like my new wand.
Jesus!
Sir?
Will thou stop?
Oh my god, I'm losing HP.
I feel like I should heal.
Let me find a safe spot.
Safe spot, safe spot.
Oh my god, there's enemies everywhere.
Oh, he's blocking.
This motherfucker is somehow blocking everything.
Okay, I'm gonna heal.
Heal me up, heal me up, heal me up, heal me up.
Good, good, good, good.
What's this?
Pheromone?
Sure.
Give me a Berserkium.
I hit him.
Okay, I'm getting him lower.
What's happening?
Hello?
Got him.
600... oh, Jesus!
I'm stuck, I'm stuck!
Water, water, water.
Oh my god.
Okay, his shield is back, his shield is back.
Okay, just use the teleport more.
Teleport around.
There we go.
And then we hide, we hide until the shield is back down.
Oh god, his spells do a lot of damage.
I'm almost dead.
Oh, fuck me.
What's that?
Pheromone?
That has to be... oh, that's Pheromone.
Okay.
No, wait.
That was Berserkium.
Some of it is Berserkium.
Dude, we're fucked.
We're fucked.
I'm scared.
What's that?
Concentrate of mana.
Dude, concentrate of mana is good.
Oh, shit.
I'm fucking dead here.
I'm dead here.
I gotta get out, I gotta get out, I gotta get out.
We're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving, we're leaving!
Just go!
Holy shit, he's after me!
I was ready for this.
God damn it.
I expected this.
I told you, it could only go downhill.
Holy shit, what a boss, man.
Well, we go again.
That was tough.
Wow, he did a lot of damage.
Okay, next time I'm coming back there, I'm gonna fucking kill him.
But we gotta get back there with more HP.
And a better wand, because holy shit, our wand sucked dick.
That was, like, that's the thing I told you.
The thing about this run that we just had, we had a shitty ass wand.
Like, we did no damage.
It was actually insane.
What's this?
Oh, burst of air.
You know what, maybe I'll try to play with that a bit.
It doesn't look like someone just going, you know, and it's just gonna be a little bit of wind.
Do we have something hiding?
We do.
I know your tricks by now, game.
That's right.
Let me in.
Fuck.
This is actually not the best way to do this, because now it's buried.
Or is it?
Hemis!
Where did it go?
Oh my god, and now I'm on... What's this?
Oh my god, it's polymorphine.
I don't want that in my flask.
Ah, my... There it is, there it is.
I see it.
Can you stop?
Oh, now I'm a sheep.
Maybe you can sneak past enemies if you're a sheep.
I haven't thought about that.
Like, if you polymorph yourself for long enough, maybe you can get past enemies.
Whoops, nice.
Bit of gold.
Whoa!
That was close.
You almost just messed up my shit.
I keep wanting to press this wand to teleport, but I don't have a teleport wand anymore.
So I'm glad I don't press it.
I have the discipline, okay?
What's in here?
Nothing.
Oh, actually, we can dig.
Watch this.
There we go.
What's up, Hemis?
They're here to welcome me to the hemisphere.
Hurta?
Give me your gold and all your belongings, please.
What is with all this sand?
Why is there so much sand?
At this point, I should stop asking these questions, because I don't get an answer, I don't think.
You know?
It's just there.
You just have sand.
Is that gold?
Hey!
Sweet.
But dude, last run was insane.
We learned so much.
It was crazy.
I do feel like maybe I jinxed myself a little bit by saying that shit was gonna go downhill, and then it became a self-fulfilling prophecy.
You know what I mean?
If I hadn't said anything, maybe I would have handled that whole situation better.
Mentally, I mean.
Got him.
Dude, I'm sort of owning these guys right now.
Yeah, and a Hemis.
I should try the smoke.
Let me try the smoke.
Oh, I'm trying this.
Wait, how much damage?
Six damage is actually kind of a lot.
What?
How's the range?
Range is not bad.
Let's say it's like medium good.
Mediocre.
That's nice.
I like it.
Nice!
Fireball?
Or fire bolt?
Right, fire bolts.
We can dick with that.
What happens if I blow on this?
Nothing.
But we can do this.
Shit, didn't mean to do that.
I keep thinking I have water in that bottle.
I really need to empty this and get some water.
Like right here.
Let me empty this somewhere.
Or should I empty this?
Maybe here.
Get it out of here.
In fact, let me pull more of this guy.
Hey, come here.
Let me fuck him up now.
Wait, that was only one shot.
Did I just discover an insane way to kill enemies?
I dealt three damage and he died.
It's still a meat of an innocent creature.
Wait a minute.
Why would it say that?
That's oddly specific sounding.
What happens if I eat the meat of an innocent creature?
Hold on, we got to test this.
How do I get... Oh man, I can't get rid of that polymorphine very well, can I?
I... Damn it.
Shit.
All right, grab some water.
Meat of an innocent... The first thing I thought of when I read that, by the way, was that let me bring it to an altar and sec... Like putting a sheep on an altar, you know what I mean?
Or like sacrifice a goat to the gods or something.
Maybe that's something you can do.
There we go.
Look at this.
Mix it all up.
Whoops.
And now I can grab a bunch of water.
Advanced strategies here.
Go this way.
Dude, I could immediately... Yo!
I could immediately get into the dark cave and grab extra health.
All I need is a worm.
I can do this at the start of every run.
Dude, that's actually insane.
Oh wait, I guess I need to go up the tree.
But I can do that.
I can do that right now.
Hold on, I'm gonna do that right now.
Why would I not do that right now?
Ah, hold on, there's a chest.
We're gonna delay that operation just a bit.
How do I get in there?
Probably go around here.
Somehow that guy died to one shot.
That's cool.
Maybe I killed him.
Jesus!
Sometimes these guys are ultra hard to kill.
When they get too close, man, it's bad for you.
We gotta eat some more mushrooms.
There we go.
Okay, so the best way to get to that chest...
I know exactly how to get to that chest the best way.
Watch this.
Oh nice, invisiblium.
Pretty cool.
I'm gonna show you the best way here.
I actually didn't realize this before, but I do now.
Also, what is it?
How good is this wand?
Oh, it's a shuffle wand, never mind.
Hate shuffle wands.
We're gonna dig to it from the bottom.
No, there we go.
Nice!
Yo, this is a sick start.
Now I need to not lose HP.
Don't be an idiot.
Play it safe now.
I mean, we always play it safe, but of course.
Even more safe.
Okay, let's go up and grab some worm blood.
That's gonna be part of the main routine now, I think.
Oh, and we can also go on top of the mountain now and grab that health too.
Oh man, what a start.
Look at this mana recharge on this.
That sucks.
Nice.
Here we go.
I wonder if I can melt the snow here by just holding the wand close to it.
This is a fire wand.
Doesn't look like it.
Oh, it's gonna take a bit.
I need to be very precise in my shots here.
So far, so good.
Sick.
Thank you.
And we can eat.
No, I'm not gonna do that, actually.
Let's go back here.
Wait.
Maximum health to 175?
Wait, already?
Wait a minute.
We picked up...
Did we pick up two hearts already?
Holy shit, this is a great start.
Wow.
Even better than I thought.
And then everything shakes.
Scary stuff.
What's happening here?
Oh, and there's even one.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hold on.
Let me check the map.
Oh no, that wasn't HP, unfortunately.
But there is a tablet right there.
But that's not HP.
Whoop, didn't mean to do that.
Back in the game.
Now we go up.
Go here.
The only thing I'm worried about now is, can I comfortably kill this worm without it fucking me up?
I actually didn't think about that.
Hmm.
This is a bad idea.
I actually don't want to fuck my run up right now.
That was, this would be terrible.
Let me think.
Okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
Oh yeah, oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna put the worm here.
Maybe I can gently put it down even.
Yes.
I'm gonna destroy this egg with a bomb.
Hopefully that's enough to also damage the guy coming out.
I guess this will be an experiment.
In fact, I'll do two bombs after each other.
Oh shit, he's burning, he's burning.
Don't kill me!
You...
Shit.
Oh!
I thought I'm gonna die, I'm gonna die for sure!
Come on.
Holy shit!
Okay, okay, never mind.
We're not doing this at the start of every run.
I changed my mind.
This is way too dangerous.
Nope, nope.
We did it once and that's it.
No more.
God damn.
Okay, for some reason I expected that to be way easier.
It wasn't.
This was a terrible idea.
I've learned my lesson.
I have some worm blood now.
Also, I could eat it right here.
Oh, but I still need to... oh no.
With six HP, dude, I think I may have fucked up.
It's over.
I gotta go through the portal.
Yeah.
That was also badly played on my part.
I could have dodged that much better.
In my mind, I was like, oh yeah, I have teleport one and all that, but I don't have any of that shit.
I am a shitty mage at this point.
And that's the truth.
But I'm gonna try.
Let me quickly go to... see how far I can go west.
You know?
Maybe it's possible.
I just need to be super careful around enemies.
Hold on.
Next you see here.
Right, so I have to go a little down.
It's like... okay, I see.
This is the real test of my map now.
I have to go down and then left.
Because the tree is blocking the upper part.
Okay, there's nothing here.
I am so wary of just the smallest thing like that, you see?
Oh, I don't want to empty my water, actually, because it contains worm blood that I need.
I'm scared of emptying that bottle.
Be careful.
Let me go here.
What is that sound I'm hearing?
What the hell is that sound?
Enemy.
It's a hemy's.
Multiple hemy.
Got him.
I'm not gonna pick that up.
I'm a scaredy cat.
Toxic sludge.
Yikes.
Let me go above.
That's a bad idea, isn't it?
That's a shotgun man I hear.
Hello, come here.
Oh, okay.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you, melee.
He punched me in the face.
I didn't know he could do that.
Fuck you, man.
All right, that's okay.
We learned a very valuable lesson here.
Don't fuck with the worms in the beginning.
I think that's a very valuable lesson to learn.
And now we've learned it.
Shit!
I just set myself on fire.
But it's okay.
I lost five HP.
Oh wait, can I not get up there?
Come on.
Yeah, barely.
Nice.
Sweet.
Damn it, that was such a good start to a run though, you know?
If it wasn't for that damn worm.
I shouldn't have done that.
I should have thought.
Thank you.
I was tempted to bring that tablet up above, but it's such a pain to get up there.
So I'm not gonna do it.
What's that?
All right, a charm effect.
I still don't understand how that works when it's on me, you know?
I understand when I put it on enemies, but other than that, it's a bit mysterious.
Sup, mines.
Hemisphere, I'm back again.
It's my favorite start I want.
The energy sphere.
It's so powerful.
Look, one shot.
And it's so fast and quick and nice and delicious.
How can you not love the energy sphere?
Oh, shit.
Oh, my chaos ensues immediately.
Wow, a bunch of enemies just appeared out of nowhere.
I guess I, you know, I can only blame myself because I was chasing the gold.
I was chasing the gold, I was just jumped into nothingness.
You know, I had dollar signs in my eyes.
And that's why I just took a bunch of damage.
Don't do that.
Fucking don't do that.
You greedy fuck.
Oh, wait, I don't have water.
Hmm.
I really need to be more disciplined here.
Let me grab that water.
That's blocked, but that's no problem.
Oh, actually, I'm gonna make a hole here and kill these guys in the meantime.
Or at the same time, not in the meantime.
In the average time.
In the median time.
I spot a wand.
Would love to have a peek at that.
Oh, wait, I also need to update my deaths here.
I think it was at 61 now.
I'm gonna make a hole here.
Wasn't enough.
Got some gold out of it, though.
Nice.
Oh, that was totally worth it.
What?
What is this?
Circle of shielding.
I don't know if I've ever had that one.
I've had circle of stillness.
No, I have had this one.
This is actually pretty dope.
I think that reflects projectiles.
Not entirely sure, but I think that's what happens.
Dead in there.
What's going on up here?
A small Huerta.
Ah, is that?
Aha!
Yay!
We can repair that later.
This is great.
What is this?
Peat.
I think I looked that up once.
It's some kind of dirty water, I think.
I actually hate these enemies.
For some reason, I have trouble dodging their projectiles.
It's because of their rate of fire.
That's what does it.
That's what makes it so hard for me.
It's like rate of fire combined with the slow movement of the projectiles.
Really fucks with me.
Nice.
Where did that guy go?
Oh, hello.
Neat.
I
need to water everything.
Another wand.
Rejoice.
Okay, don't chase that gold.
We learned our lesson.
Do not go into the unknown.
Oh, I can't get through here.
Yes, I can.
Oh, oh, oh, watch this, watch this.
Hold on, let me take care of this guy first.
Uh oh, uh oh.
I'm gonna fuck this guy up with water.
Sup, nerd?
Oh, and you come from there?
Flanking me here.
There you go, buddy.
You like that?
Huh?
Come on now.
If I kill him with water, he will also not drop a bunch of lava.
Look at that.
Clean.
What do we got?
A bomb.
Not bad.
Not bad at all.
Oh, damn.
He almost fucked up my shit.
Okay.
Can't go that way.
Got a good amount of money already and 60 HP.
That's not bad.
That means I only lost 40% of my HP.
From the starter HP, that is.
Get some water.
We could try and go steal that HP on the right, but that angers the boss.
And that's a bit risky, isn't it?
Maybe I should not do that.
I'm tempted though.
Oh, you died.
Uh, that is toxic sludge.
Give me money.
I can grab that.
Come on.
Isn't that the coolest thing?
I can't get over how nice that is.
We can mix things like this.
I wonder if there's other combinations.
I really ought to try.
I feel like I've tried a bunch of things, but nothing really happens.
It's like when I put chemicals together, they always just float on top of each other.
That is the only real reaction that I've been able to get.
Just put water in toxic sludge, you know?
It's a frost man.
No, wait, it's electricity?
No, that's electricity.
Jesus Christ.
Let's get the fuck out of here.
Oh, so wait, if it's electricity, what is he weak against?
Let me think.
Maybe fire.
I'm not sure actually how that works.
I'm not dude.
Maybe water.
That's bad, right?
For him.
How am I gonna...
Damn.
Dude, that's crazy.
Yo, what the fuck is this?
Look at that.
What?
They're shelves of potions.
Dude, I can't die here.
I need to see what's going on.
Okay, that dude is clearly down there.
We need to bomb him.
Did you die?
You did not die.
Look at his little peephole here.
We can bomb that.
Yeah, dude.
See ya, bitch.
Let's see what the hell's going on here.
Look at this.
Like what?
The actual F?
Never seen this.
Holy shit.
What's that?
Fire potion?
Oh my god, there's all kinds of things.
Chaotic water.
You know what?
Water.
Give me that.
Give me a full one.
Worm pheromone.
No, wait.
I thought it was worm blood.
I don't want worm pheromone, I don't think.
At least.
Chaotic polymorphine.
Ambrosia?
That's nice.
Pheromone.
Polymorphine.
Worm pheromone.
Levitation.
Oh, you know what?
Doesn't this almost look like a...
I want to say cauldron, but it's not really... it's like a natural cauldron?
Is this... hold on.
How crazy is this, by the way?
I was just saying before.
I want to try mixing more things and the game's like, all right bro, here you go.
Try... go nuts.
Here's a bunch of shit.
Have fun.
How about we try and mix up some shit here?
I actually want to try this.
I want to get rid of that lava though, because that makes me uncomfortable.
Let's do a bit of this.
That looks good to me.
No more lava.
What was this?
Ambrosia, right.
Okay, uh, let's put some levitation in there.
Mix it.
Okay, I'm gonna put all kinds of shit in here.
Wait, um...
Levitation.
Water's already in there.
Let me gently put down the flask.
Gently.
Fuck me.
Well, now it's mixed.
Damn it all.
Chaotic polymorph... let's try and pour that in.
May as well just do that from now on.
Nice colors going on.
Barramone goes in.
We're making a crazy mix of things here.
Okay.
Polymorphine.
Yes.
Oh, there's just sort of float down there.
They need to be destroyed.
Oh my god, this is a mess.
Mix it, mix it, mix it, mix it.
What else have I not put in fire?
Let's put some fire in there, huh?
Let's see how that works.
Burn it!
Burn the solution.
Add heat.
Okay, what about... what is this one?
A pheromone?
I don't know if I tried that one.
Release it.
It's just all layered.
There's no reactions here.
Hmm.
Very weird, huh?
Oh, and nice heart as well.
What a cool level.
Dude, what is going on?
I've never seen this shit.
That's so cool that they keep throwing new things in here.
That guy has a wand.
Look at that.
That scares me a little bit.
In fact...
Nope.
Make a hole over there.
This is a mess.
I'm scared of what that guy is able to do.
Okay, he's dead.
Good.
Ah, okay.
Circle of shielding.
Hmm.
Is it better than this wand?
I don't think so.
They're both equally shitty.
All right, well, now I've seen that.
I can't help but think.
Maybe there was some kind of puzzle there, you know?
Maybe you had to put in a specific liquid down in the middle.
Like some of the other puzzles we've seen.
Actually, last time we had to fill something with water, remember?
And we got something.
What do I have now?
Fire potion?
Oh, I need to be careful because that fire potion is in my...
Normally, I have water there potion spot.
I'm gonna get in here.
Oh, I can't get destroyed that, but I can do it from below.
All from the top.
I would say from the... Let's do it from below.
Seems safer.
Oh, hello there.
My dude.
I see you up there.
Ah, fuck.
This needs to be timed perfectly.
Oh my god, I'm perfect.
What can I say?
Jesus Christ, we got a pure chainsaw on our hands.
I will take it.
It's also a non-shuffle.
Oh, but it has 10 mana charge.
The wand sucks, but the stuff is good.
I should be replacing some of this with water.
Hold on.
Concentrated mana I kind of want.
I don't want fire.
Maybe I get rid of fire.
Let's put the fire in the oil and watch everything go nuts.
That's fun.
This is just like napalm.
Isn't that basically what napalm is?
Liquid fire.
Damn.
Sweet.
Get some of that water.
Come on.
Nice.
I got it.
It's dripping gold.
What the hell?
Look at that.
It's big enough.
500 gold to my name?
Not bad.
It's quiet.
Too quiet.
The collapsed mines.
Boink.
Oh, I wish it would have hit him in the face.
It would have been glorious.
Got you.
Oh, not the frogs.
I hate those.
Good thing I just murdered them.
What's happening here?
Okay.
What is with all this polymorphine?
There's so much of it.
I don't want to check that out though.
Get the hazards out of here.
There's a frog.
Is it gonna be turned into something?
Come here.
Jump into the polymorphine.
Come on, boy.
Or that.
That works too.
That's actually a bit sketch.
Let me.
Thank you.
More polymorphine.
How did I not just catch fire?
Oh, no.
I hate this enemy so much.
It's one of the worst enemies for me.
They're just so goddamn annoying.
Give me more water.
I hear the roots of the tree.
Wait, if the layout is the same, then I can technically learn it by heart and just grab the hearts in there.
Get it?
Even though I can't see.
Oh, that's oil.
Don't like that.
Whoops.
Didn't mean to do that.
Nice.
You.
Are you hiding something in there?
Something I would like.
It's hard to tell.
I'm tempted to dig my way in.
Because I can't see what's in there.
See, this is the type of situation where the all seeing eye would be amazing.
You know, to figure out whether or not I should dig in the first place.
Yeah, I don't think there's anything in there.
I'm not gonna waste my resources.
Although I have a bunch.
Nah, fuck him.
Let's move on.
Damn, HP.
Wait, what are these guys again?
I forgot what they do.
Wait, what?
Can I pick that up?
Hold on.
Ha!
I picked up a cocktail!
What is the difference?
Can I fill the cocktail with...
Oh wait, I need to equip it first.
Wait, what?
Oh no!
I...
Okay.
It blows up.
That makes sense, I guess.
These guys throw things that blow up.
That's funny.
You could pick up the grenades, basically, of the enemy.
What is blocking?
Oh, a body part.
Did he die?
I think he died.
What's that?
I hate sometimes.
It doesn't show me when I mouse over what it is.
Whoa!
Excuse me!
Water it!
Good, good, good.
Acceleration, I actually like that.
I could go through.
I'm tempted.
34 HP.
You know, I could explore it just a tiny bit more.
I'm close to the portal.
What's that?
Molten metal!
I've never seen that.
I guess I should not touch that.
That seems like it.
Wait, molten...
I was going to say, isn't that lava?
No, that's molten rock.
Yeah, that's different.
Molten metal.
I wonder what produced that.
Well, I guess metal being melted.
But you know, you know what I mean.
Tell me there's not a stray him is down here that I didn't see.
Okay, fine.
Sometimes they stack on top of each other and you don't expect one to be alive when you arrive, you know?
It can happen.
It happened to me.
Could happen to you.
I don't think I explored the right side very much.
We should definitely check that out.
I can get in there.
No, I can't.
Yes, I can.
Oh my God.
What a shitty bomb.
What is actually wrong with me?
That was the worst throw of all time.
Can I get up here?
Yes, I can.
I can go around.
You stay wet all the time.
Protection from fire.
We've got him.
Oh, many him is.
That can be dangerous if I'm not careful here.
Why there's so many?
I don't care.
It's money.
Sweet.
Just murdered a whole fucking generation of him is.
And I went out of my way to do it.
I was like, Oh, I see you there.
And then I took a whole detour just to murder you.
I murdered them.
That's how evil I am.
Look how they're stacking.
That's so much money.
What was that?
Someone threw a blue projectile.
Wait, was that my own projectile?
Actually, never mind.
I think it was mine.
It just looked like it came from somewhere else.
Not me.
Okay, I'm glad that's over there.
The worst enemies.
Did I get him?
I did.
Did you see that control descent just then?
Skills.
I have a thousand gold.
What the heck?
I have almost never been this rich so early.
This is a very rare thing.
I should probably...
You know what?
It's time.
We should go through the portal.
Let's do it.
With all this money, we can buy the whole world.
Look at the layers.
Worm pheromone, chaotic polymorphine, polymorphine water, pheromone, and some levitation, I think, on top.
Elop, of course.
Let's see what we got.
Triplicate bolt is nice.
Long distance cast could be cool.
This one could be cool depending on the perks we get.
Let's see it.
Projectile, either.
Projectiles to fly into a small sector behind of you disappear.
Er... no.
Enemies explode upon death, but you gain immunity to explosive damage.
Wait.
Uh... hold on.
How is this not just explosion immunity, but better?
Because if all enemies explode, isn't that just good for me?
Well, I guess it's debatable, right?
Because if they explode, I guess a bunch of fire is created and I can catch fire.
Permanent shield, I like that one.
I'm taking that.
That is a crazy good perk.
Loving that one.
Okay, let's see what we got.
We got a bunch of chainsaws.
That means that we potentially...
can make a really fast wand.
Let's see here.
Maybe even these.
They add a bunch of castellato, that's the issue.
But this... okay, this one has...
This one is shuffle?
Let me actually just try something.
I know it's shuffle, but fuck it.
Let's see what happens.
Okay.
Let me just get rid of these again.
Oh!
So... wait, what?
Look at this!
It shoots pump, pump, recharge, pump, pump, recharge.
But when I add this...
Whoops.
Now it's going...
It's much more consistent.
Oh yeah, that makes sense.
Because we remove recharge rate.
Of course.
I'm an idiot.
Yes, good.
And it's random.
So is it then?
Interesting.
Yeah, well, okay.
I was expecting this to go really fast.
Because of all these chainsaws.
But honestly, I think there's something about the chainsaw that I just don't understand.
Because for some reason, it also didn't have an effect on the last one in the last run, even though it should have.
In my mind at least, you know, it's a very mysterious spell.
I don't quite understand it.
Let me try something else.
Let's try on this one.
So it has a very shitty mana charge.
Let's see how bad it is.
So what if I add this?
Does this do anything?
If I add a bunch?
Yeah, it's hard to tell.
But the mana recharge is insanely slow.
Yikes.
Quick test.
Instead of having two of these here, what if we add one of these like that?
It's actually slower because it's going energy sphere, poof.
Energy sphere, poof.
Makes a little chainsaw, poof.
So I think what we need is a double spell to combine them.
I just don't have that here, unfortunately.
Kind of want sparkles.
Is that crazy?
A triplicate bolt could also be nice.
A bit too scattery for me.
Yeah, we need that thing that reduces scatter for those ones.
Unless we go up close and personal.
I don't need to put this here.
No, they haven't had the energy spheres is the best one we have.
Okay, what else do I want to buy?
Honestly, I'm not really sure I want to buy much more.
You know what, I'm going to get the rock.
That's not...
And this one.
Yeah, it's so cheap anyway.
I have so much money.
I think that's it.
We can go.
Yeah, let's fucking do it.
Let's go on.
The coal pits.
It's time.
Let's find a great wand here, huh?
Speak enough.
Does this be a great wand?
Always cast circle of transmogrification.
Something tells me that's bad.
Quadruple scatter sounds cool.
Burst of air may be cool.
Actually, this one sucks.
This one is actually not bad.
Oh, it is bad because of this.
But I'll take it because of these spells.
Until I find something else, at least.
The wheel is spinning.
Say what now?
Oh god, oh god.
Why is it spinning?
Why are you spinning, sir?
Okay, it's slowing down.
I'm scared of that dude.
I'm gonna ignore him for now.
Oh man, I have a mosquito bite.
In between my fingers.
The little crevice.
It's so annoying.
So itchy.
Oh wait.
Wait, it doesn't...
Oh, it doesn't transmogrify me.
Let me try it on an enemy.
Maybe not that one.
I'm scared of those.
I love this permanent shield.
It's fantastic.
Actually, I don't want to try it on any enemy.
They're all scary.
If I can find a himis, then I'll do it.
Or something like a horta.
Maybe that guy.
Let's try on this dude right here.
Well,
it does exactly what it advertises.
Pretty cool, I'd say.
Let's try again.
Dude, this is actually...
Bro, is this permanent?
Because if that's the case, this is actually sick.
Hello?
Look, they instant die.
Meat of an innocent creature, eat it.
You feel like you're future worm food, cause ingesting meat of an innocent creature.
Oh, okay.
I don't like that description.
That makes me not happy.
Don't like that.
Yeah, fly into that.
Yes, what do you got now?
Nothing.
How is this not broken AF?
Am I crazy?
This is an insane wand.
I looked at that at first and thought, ah, that's crap.
No, I don't think so anymore.
Does that work on bosses?
Imagine that.
Definitely gotta try.
Oh my god, you are annoying.
Oh, you're annoying.
Holy shit.
Will you go away?
Leave a poor man alone, will you?
Didn't that look like a guy with a flaming head?
You bastard.
Yeah, I could turn into a sheep.
Actually, I want to see how long they last.
Oh, he died, nevermind.
Cause if this is permanent, then it's actually kind of...
Dude.
So when it say it always casts that, I don't think I'm able to modify it such that I can, for example, cast it at a long range, right?
Cause it's always first.
It gets cast before anything else.
So it's always at my position.
Cause I thought maybe if you put that on a...
Ooh, dude.
If you had that spell and you put it on a trigger so that when you hit something, it's now a sheep.
And then they instant die.
How is that not insane?
I feel like that sounds like a crazy combination.
Hello, that works.
Look at this tuxing environment.
Oh, fuck me.
Okay, we're fine.
We actually have a bunch of HP.
When I find mushrooms, I'm going to eat them.
And I'm going to be tripping balls.
In fact, isn't there a mushroom area to the west of here?
Bone dust.
What?
Can I eat it?
Eat this.
I can't.
You know what?
I'm going to try to eat more things.
Just in general.
Because let's say I never tried eating the fungus.
I never would have experienced that, right?
We should eat everything we see.
Okay, go this way now.
That's the wand we found.
The wheel is still spinning.
It's somehow speeding up now.
There's no such thing as a free meal.
Oh, oh, wait a minute.
No.
You have been completely nullified, sir.
Yo, that's actually sick.
Look at this.
Tell me that's not crazy good.
Nest.
I kind of want to try and eat it.
Oh, no.
Bro, this circle is wild.
He didn't want none of that, it seems.
Wand in here.
Oh my god.
Can I...
Ah, you know, I should have taken the spell ref...
No, I shouldn't have taken it.
I think it's a good thing I saved that.
You know?
If I find a circle of healing or whatever it's called, I'm gonna... I can refresh it later, you know?
So can I do any digging at all?
No.
I am unable.
How are you not dead?
I sorely need digging capabilities.
This is getting a little ridiculous.
That guy just died one shot.
It pushed me into the fire and then I was stuck.
That was scary.
What a death trap.
Okay, I found my way in here.
That's good.
Boink!
You like that?
Fucking sheeps.
That is tele... I don't want that.
Uh, go west because we saw a wand.
Go west where the lands are green.
Aha!
Nice.
What do we got?
Yo!
That's great!
I love that.
For future wand building, we're gonna do some good stuff with that.
Uh, yes.
Oh, okay.
There was a tiny pixel of fire there.
Let's wait for all this to blow over.
Every time I say that sentence, in my mind, I have that shot where they dolly zoom in on the guy drinking the coffee in the pub, you know?
From that one movie.
Shit, man.
I can't remember anything.
You know what I'm talking about.
Come on, man.
I need some...
Give me... Wait, what's this?
Hold on.
Look how long this lasts!
Is this infinite?
You could totally just fill a level with that, and you're safe from, like, every single corner.
Just put a circle there.
How is that not broken?
Fuck, I need digging!
Can't go anywhere.
Let's see if we have some luck down here.
Hello.
That's right.
Heh heh.
Man, it's a good thing I don't get turned into a sheep, huh?
That actually makes me think.
If I get polymorph'd...
Will I...
Wait.
I just had a lot of dread.
If I get turned into a sheep, will I also insta-die?
Because I haven't... I don't think I've noticed that yet.
But now I'm starting to scare or, like, be afraid of that situation happening.
If that is indeed how that works.
Because then I suddenly gained a lot of fear for that.
I'm scared now.
I'm very scared.
Oh!
Dude, what a long ass want!
That's a long boy.
We need to check that out immediately.
If we can't even get in there.
See ya.
Oh, we didn't even die.
What a survivor.
Okay, so the plan is now to find a wand that can dig.
So I can get in to find this wand.
So I can hopefully find something that digs even better.
In other words, we need... we need dig.
I'm not thin enough.
Can I grab that gold?
I'm too thick.
Fuck!
I...
I refuse to leave this place before I somehow get to that wand.
I swear to god, I will find a way.
Can I...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Chainsaw?
Oh no, that's not gonna work.
Yeah, chainsaw.
Coal?
Can I though?
Actually.
Yeah, you kind of can.
This could work in theory.
At least for the coal that's stacked like that.
I don't know about coal in the...
Let me test here.
Does that work?
It works!
Question it.
Oh, there's actually only a tiny bit of stuff to dig through.
We can do that.
I am undertaking this.
I'm doing it.
I'm gonna have slime fall on me.
Or like toxic sludge fall on my head in a second here.
That's fine.
I'm gonna be ready to get out of the way.
Not quite ready.
Almost ready.
Well, that's fine.
Now, we dig even more.
Come on now.
How am I not getting in yet?
A bit more up here maybe?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Almost, almost.
Yes!
Holy fucking balls!
Chainspell causes a projectile to cast a copy of itself
upon expiring.
Up to five times?
Caused a projectile to cast a copy of itself upon expiring.
Okay.
That's interesting.
Critical on bloody enemies, essence to power.
I like this one.
Oh, dude, speed up!
Nice!
Oh, and teleport.
All these things are good.
This is a great wand.
Maybe I'll replace it with...
Hold on.
Yeah, replace this one.
Hell yeah, dude!
That's mine!
Oops.
Don't walk on that.
I'm scared to cast this.
It's also shuffled.
Yeah, I don't know about that one, man.
That seems a little, you know, a little not good.
Oh, but I can't dig at all now, right?
Shit.
So if I shoot this wand, what is actually gonna happen?
It's honestly just a teleport wand, isn't it?
Oh.
Okay.
Yeah, it casts a copy of itself upon expiring up to five times.
That's wild.
And a shuffle.
It's complete mayhem.
In other words.
That thing is trouble, dude.
Look, these are still going!
These circles last forever.
They're permanent!
I have some crazy wands, dude.
Hello.
Can I...
Through walls?
Oh my lord.
Even better.
Okay, I think it's time we move on.
This is cool.
I have a lot of money.
We got the wands.
We need digging.
Let's go.
Hell yeah.
I'm gonna save this healing as well.
Not taking that yet.
Let's see what we got.
Glowing lands could be nice.
Digging bolt could've...
Oh, this one is nice.
Reduce spread.
100% we're getting that.
Let's see.
Oh, is that...
We have a rock!
Unlimited spells?
Oh, vampirism!
Oh, I'm conflicted now!
Oh, what's this?
Low reg...
No, fuck that shit.
No, I gotta go with this.
Wait...
I gotta go with that.
There's no way I'm not going with that.
We gotta go with that.
Hey, yo!
That is fantastic.
Oh, but wait a second.
Hold your horses.
Also, you know what?
Let's make a nice little...
Okay, watch this.
We're gonna do something...
That has never been seen before.
Something nice.
We're gonna...
This is the pile of chainsaws.
We're gonna separate all of these.
We have a bomb here.
Then we have...
Let's put TNT here.
We keep it organized in this house.
Okay?
There.
Maybe this one goes here.
Then we have a last...
Maybe that one.
There.
Just to make some room.
Now we can go pick them up when we need them.
Isn't that cool?
I think it is.
What's this again?
Heavy spread.
I like that.
Essence to power is cool.
I like that too.
I like this one.
We don't need all of these teleport balls.
So, the ones we don't need go in the water.
That's the plan.
We technically just need one, right?
So...
There we go.
Uh, wait.
Did I accidentally...
Oh, there we
go.
One of them.
Good.
So, here's my question.
If glowing lance expires on this one, is that just gonna go nuts and shoot multiple?
Wait.
Oh, that's...
Okay, that's kind of scary, actually.
But how much damage?
Why can't I see damage there?
Hey?
Okay.
Usually, I'm able to see damage.
Would it not realize that could damage me?
Okay, that's good to know.
Holy fuck!
That's scary.
Don't play with that.
Now, the rock, I'm pretty sure, cannot damage me.
We tested that.
And we have infinite rocks now.
Is this gonna make four...
Five...
Is this gonna make five rocks?
No, wait.
When it expires.
So, what does that mean when the rock is, like, destroyed?
Let's test.
Yeah, it hasn't expired yet.
When this rock expires at some point.
When the half-life of the...
I don't even know.
The stuff inside the rock over enough fucking millions of years when it finally dissolves, another rock appears.
And that happens five times.
Okay.
What else we got?
Can I make a...
I need to make a damage wand.
I need to make a main wand here.
So, energy sphere.
No, wait.
This one.
Interesting.
Wait, no, no.
Okay, that's a bit chaotic.
I don't like the way this is...
I'm trying to think, can I make something cool with this modifier of when it expires, it creates five copies.
You know?
What could be super...
Maybe this one.
Because this one is...
Let's see.
Yeah, it's...
Honestly, it's like a...
It's like a trigger.
That's what this is.
It's a trigger times five.
That's what that means.
What would be not...
Maybe...
Hey.
Oh, oh, oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Didn't we...
Where's the digging bolt we found?
I hear this.
Hold on now.
I have an idea.
Dig, dig, dig, dig.
What if we were to do this?
Wait, what's...
What's with the spread on this?
Why is it random as fuck?
A.
Oh, is it doing it five times?
But it's like so fast, you don't even see it.
I guess that's what's happening.
Okay, maybe I don't want to play with this too much.
It's kind of scary now.
But watch this.
If I were to do this and a rock, we don't have homing, but...
Hey.
That's it?
I expected this to be a little better.
We need homing.
We need to find homing ASAP.
That is already a crazy thing if we can do that.
That will make this run.
Uh, so for now we need to do something temporary, something else.
What can we make?
Let's think.
Let's see how good...
This one is actually not bad, right?
370 mana max, 100...
But yeah, it always cast the sheep.
That's actually fine, because I'm not affected by that.
That's okay.
It cast the sheep.
And maybe the triple kit is nice for that, because if I combine this with turning enemies into sheep, and they just need one hit...
There it is, right?
They die.
That's it.
They just die.
So...
Actually, let me test something real quick.
If I put this here...
Okay, still gonna cast it where I am.
So this modifier is always first.
No meta ones.
Okay.
And now this is just here.
This is actually kind of annoying.
Hmm...
But it's gonna be annoying to shoot this wand, because it's gonna deploy one of these every single time.
Maybe I'll use this as a utility wand to just deploy this and nothing else.
You know, I'll have no spells on this.
No spells.
And then we use some other wand.
So let's say I just put this in there.
How does this look?
Yeah, looks like that.
This wand has a lot of mana, but a shitty recharge.
This is like a decent wand.
You know, it's not the best, not the worst either.
But with this...
It's not terrible as a start, you know.
I'm just scared that I don't have enough damage just in general here.
I mean, I do have a rock I can summon.
I can drop a rock on enemies' heads, I guess, if I'm above them.
That's one way to do it.
It's just not very effective, right?
Seems a little dumb.
Hmm.
But then again, I have this that I can utilize.
I don't know what to do.
Nice that we have that at least.
I like that we have the teleport.
That's solid to have.
Oh, we also have all of these.
Oh, let's think here.
Let me actually...
Hold on a second.
What does this do again?
Cast two spells.
One ahead of and one behind the caster.
Oh.
Right.
That's bifurcation.
We have chainsaws.
Oh, wait a minute.
Can we maybe chainsaw on this one and make something crazy happen?
What is the limit on this one right now?
It's the recharge.
Hey, that's exactly what we need.
Hold on.
So if I take these...
That could be interesting.
It's kind of a mess.
I'm not sure I like the mess.
What is the limiting factor here now?
Let's add some more stuff.
Do I even have more stuff?
Maybe I do this.
No, it's shuffle.
Damn it.
Maybe this is better.
Oh, wow.
That cost 110 mana.
Wow.
Okay.
That's a lot.
Maybe glowing lands, my beloved.
You know, that is a good one.
With speed, maybe.
Hey, that's solid.
That is actually solid.
I think I like that.
118, 25...
But on this one.
Oh, it did cast two...
That's fine, though.
Oh, yeah.
This is totally...
Like the recharge doesn't matter when you're...
The mana charge speed doesn't matter when your recharge time is this high anyway.
That's what I was trying to say.
I like this.
This is a good want.
It's a good want.
Now we can have...
Let's have one where we summon a rock.
Yeah.
And this one is going to be our sheep want.
It sounds a little dumb, but that's how it is.
We have a sheep one.
We have a sheep stick.
These are nice to have.
Oh, we need a teleport one, of course.
That can be that one, I guess.
So we don't have a rock want.
This one sucks.
I could put rock on this, but I'm kind of scared of that.
I don't know why.
I just am.
Well, dude, we need digging.
Can we dig with anything here?
I mean, chainsaw, technically.
Oh, bombs.
We have infinite bombs!
We have infinite spells!
Oh, we have digging bowl, too, of course.
But that's the thing.
Okay, why is this so weird, though?
Why does it shoot in such weird, random directions?
Spread is one on this.
Like, look at that.
It shot completely off-center there.
And behind me, it doesn't make any sense.
If I shoot this one, though...
it's always in front.
Damn, what a mess.
That's interesting.
Dude.
Let me test my theory.
Holy shit, it actually works.
Who needs digging when you can go through walls?
Yo.
That's cool.
We're totally doing that.
The hell?
Yeah, dude!
Oh.
Okay, so teleport is done.
Damage is done.
Now, this wand...
What do we put on that?
We can put some digging on it, I guess.
Just to have, like, a small amount of digging.
It's always nice to have.
But wha- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if we do...
Hold on.
I have some stuff over here, as well, that I want to bring with me.
I think I like this one.
Critical on bloody enemies.
That's nice to have, I think.
Uh...
That was that one.
I'm trying to think.
If we can somehow digging bolts at a distance, but we don't have any triggers.
Except this is a trigger in itself, right?
If I do that...
What does that actually do?
It just alternates, of course.
You know, maybe I won't have anything in this wand.
Maybe this wand sucks.
I've decided this wand sucks.
I don't like this wand.
I don't like the shuffle.
I've decided it goes in the trash.
So let's throw away...
Uh...
Hmm.
This one.
Put it on the floor, somewhere over here.
There we go.
And then we put...
Bomb in it.
Or TNT, what is best?
Probably bombs.
Yeah, I don't like the air.
Yet.
I mean, maybe you can make something nice with it, but for now...
I'm gonna be bombing shit.
And this is gonna make a lot of bombs, right?
Oh!
Look at that!
Now...
That's what I'm talking about!
Maybe we do it with TNT instead.
It's a little shorter lift, right?
And it's a little better in that regard.
Okay, that's it!
We go!
Should I buy another rock?
Let's buy another rock.
Get rid of...
What should I get rid of?
Oh, we have two lights.
Yeah!
Let's take two rocks.
Let's go!
Kind of want to make peace with gods if I am able to somehow.
Oh, dude!
Wait!
Watch!
Fuck yeah!
That just occurred to me!
Sup, rat?
Hello!
Oh yeah, the glowing lands!
Now we're talking!
Oh, I'm so happy!
We can go...
Look at this!
We go through walls.
Hey, guys!
You want to maybe...
Try that?
Yeah, you hate it.
Does that work on mechanical enemies?
We have to try that.
Did he just kill his friend?
Like, these levels are going to be filled with those circles at some point.
They gotta disappear after a while, right?
There's no way they just persist.
I somehow refuse to believe that.
Just for, like, a game design perspective, isn't that gonna fuck up the memory or, like, the processing of the game, which always can't calculate that all the time?
Okay, I'm actually not too heavy about the recharge time on this glowing lands wand I have here.
Not the best!
This is a nice sniper wand!
Yeah, this is a decent, decent wand.
I kind of forgot how much I loved the glowing lands.
Now I remember why I loved it so much.
I'll watch this.
Oh, okay, okay!
You know what?
Maybe that's a bit too risky.
The TNT on that wand, maybe not a good idea.
You know what?
Let me try on this.
Oh my god!
It freaking works!
I'm unstoppable.
I need to find homing.
That's my mission.
Any type of homing.
Hold on, I can just...
Oh, that's actually kind of scary.
Imagine if I accidentally blink into lava like this.
This is a bit risky, isn't it?
Yeah, that is too unreliable.
You don't want to do that.
TNT on this wand is a disaster.
But the good thing is, I can get back up!
Hmm.
Ah!
Oh no!
This guy needs to come close to me.
That's how I deal with it.
Let's see if I can turn this guy into a...
Oh my god!
It works on everything.
If this works on bosses, surely it's not gonna work on bosses.
Surely not.
There's no way.
Wait, how did this guy get turned into a sheep?
He didn't even get here.
Weird.
Where are you, sir?
There's a chest there.
A wand!
Okay.
Another shuffle wand.
Shit.
Magic arrow with trigger.
Maybe that's not bad.
You know?
I can maybe dig that.
That's not bad.
Let's remember this is here.
Where's the electricity man?
I see you.
I hate when they're below me, you know?
It's tough.
Where'd you go?
There.
Nope, there's someone else.
Wait, did the guy shoot the sheep?
I'm so scared.
I kind of want to drop on him and turn him into a sheep.
Flamox you.
Tell me he died.
Did I get him?
I don't know what... No, I didn't.
I didn't get him.
Man, the knockback on the blowing lands is out of this world.
There we go.
Such a scary enemy.
Probably one of the more scary enemies in the game.
Because they do so much damage.
And when they hit you, you actually get shocked and stunned for a while.
Makes it even worse.
Wait.
I can get through the wall.
Should I though?
Yes.
I have to remember, the glowing lands goes through walls.
Let me get rid of that, because I'm scared of it.
Why is it not leaking?
Okay, there we go.
There we go.
Oh, that's electric.
That's electric.
That's bad.
Oh wait, that's the electric thingy you can pick up.
It's the electric version of the Kiva Skibi.
Wow, you didn't die?
Ha!
Nice.
Oh wait, he had a wand!
Ch- Ah!
Shuffle wands.
Dang it.
Hmm.
I'm tempted, because...
I don't know.
This looks nice, to have those digging bolts.
Then again, I haven't been that impressed with the digging bolts.
I've been here, haven't I?
Yes.
That's that one.
Okay.
I don't want flammoxium.
Who wants that in their right mind?
Oh no.
Do we have electric man?
I'm gonna call them cable guys, from now on.
I don't know, they kind of remind me of...
of the cable guy.
Jim Carrey.
Another cable guy!
He needs two hits, I think.
From the glowing lance.
Is he- where'd he go?
Man, I knocked them back into the whole nother world.
Okay, three hits they need.
Four?
Damn, okay.
Much harder than I thought.
That guy was chopping up his friend, I guess, to eat him.
Now watch this.
Oh wait, I can show you.
Hold on, is this- is this trap gonna...
Is that gonna link to here and fuck me?
I'm actually scared.
Hold on.
Try it.
Okay, okay.
No, I don't like this.
So crazy that I can just go on the other side of the wall.
Like, look at this!
Okay, that's actually kind of scary, we gotta get out of here.
Whoo!
You gotta be absolutely sure what's on the other side before you go.
Plamoxium.
Nope.
Don't want it.
Hello!
Watch this, I can blow these up from in here.
Ah!
They lose a lot of, uh...
Come on.
There we go.
Hey, who shot me?
Dude, I just had the most genius idea.
Imagine you're facing an enemy that likes to pick up wands.
I throw the polymorph wand to him and they polymorph themselves.
Isn't that exactly what's gonna happen?
Hello?
Wait a minute.
Unless when they use it, it works on me and not on them.
That could be the scary part there.
But I'm tempted to try that.
Just because it sounds hilarious.
Okay, what do we got up here?
Kind of want a double blowing lance.
Or a triple blowing lance.
Not four though, that's too much.
That's not bad.
That means...
digging.
But it also damages me.
I mean...
Yeah, it actually not bad.
Just feels weird to throw this wand away.
It seems special, doesn't it?
It really does seem special.
But I can always come back for it, I guess, which I'll probably never do.
We all know that.
But the possibilities...
Oh man, can I just go like this?
Wow.
I have such easy access.
Unreal.
And I can edit.
Let me...
I don't even know.
Maybe I just want bombs.
I mean, Poland is nice.
But hello, bombs.
We have infinite, right?
So why wouldn't I just put bombs here?
Or there.
No, not there.
Goes up there.
And we go back in.
Look at that.
Wild.
It seems like the gods have very specific rules on what constitutes making them mad, you know?
There's this one specific spot you can't be in, which is triggering them.
What is with all these phlemoxiums?
People love that shit here.
Oh.
Hello.
My shield is saving me a lot.
Just bouncing off projectiles.
Cheers, everybody.
I have good feelings about this run.
This is very, very promising.
Where?
Oh.
So the snipers need two shots.
Those bastards.
Oh, I want, but I can just teleport in there, right?
Oh my god.
You bastard.
Stop!
This guy fucked me up.
Another sniper.
Okay, you know what?
I've had enough of your shenanigans.
Come here.
Bitch.
Oh damn, can't get in.
See, now I kind of wish I had the pollen.
Oh, unless...
That works.
A bit risky though, but it works.
Hey, multiple rocks and bubbly bounce.
Makes the projectiles shoot bubble sparks as it bounces.
I wonder how that works on rocks.
Let's try it.
Maybe a bouncing rock is maybe ill-defined.
I can't believe I haven't tried this combination earlier.
It's so obvious in hindsight.
Right?
And it's absolutely mind-blowingly good.
What's the cool part about this game?
You keep discovering all these crazy things.
Ah!
Come here!
Come on, pussy!
Oh, I can shoot you through the wall, that's right.
Don't even need to care about anything.
Oh, I see you.
See ya!
It is a bit weird to teleport around with the long-distance cast though.
You gotta get used to it, you know?
Hey, dude.
Oh, man, I need worm blood here.
That would be amazing.
You know what?
Let's go in here and fuck shit up.
I feel good about this.
Even though it's dark, we can do this.
It gets lit up when you walk.
That's the good part about this.
Did I damage you with that?
Uh...
That's a weird projectile.
Okay, I'm definitely damaging you.
You don't take a lot of damage from that.
Are you... Will you be turned into a sheep?
Come here!
Come on now!
In the circle you...
Yeah...
It is my mission to turn every enemy into sheeps.
Ouch!
Holy crap!
Just make a perimeter!
Come to me!
Come here!
Oh my god.
Someone has a wand.
Wait, this is the...
Can I just...
Wait.
Yes, I can.
For sure.
Oh my... What's this?
Cool, look, kiwi.
Uh...
Gently?
Thank you.
Oh right, I remember this.
This artifact is covered in note-shaped engravings.
And it's pulsing at a steady pace.
Is that the sound of distant music?
Okay, you know what?
I need to take a piss real bad.
I have a suspicion that if I play this music right here for long enough in this spot, maybe something will happen.
So I'm gonna use this opportunity to go take a leak while that happens.
Fear back.
Okay, nothing's happening.
I will take it with me though.
Maybe we can drop this on something later on and it will give us something.
You know, your curiosity has been rewarded type thing.
If we're lucky.
I'll just take it with me.
Okay, so there's a dude with a wand somewhere here.
And that scares me.
Dude, imagine putting a homing rock with a long-distance cast.
You could spawn rocks on the other side of walls and fuck people up.
That seems wild.
Oh my god, will you die?
Thank you.
Seems like he's taking reduced damage from whatever it is I'm doing with this.
Okay, where's the wand man?
Hmm, let's put them at junctions like that.
And lure the enemies in here.
That's right.
Where's the wand man?
We're shooting a concentrated light, I believe.
Look at that!
That was toxic.
Wait, what just happened?
I'm scared.
Just light up everything.
Aha!
Is that the dude?
Come on now, come.
Come here.
What?
Hey, he's immune to that!
Say what now?
This fucker is immune!
That's unreal.
I got him though.
His eyes went out.
What's that?
Come here.
Bye-bye.
Oh!
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
He's invisible.
Come here, come here.
Yeah, yeah!
Thank you.
Antigravity.
Ties a lifting force to a projectile.
Wow.
Oh, it's shuffle.
Everything is shuffle.
Terrible.
Fuck you.
Orb room.
We are in the snowy depths right now.
You know what?
Oh, shit.
What?
There we go, there we go.
I need to map this place.
This was called Magical Temple.
I need to sort of confirm exactly where it is.
Wait, what's that?
Is that a wand?
Hey!
That's a...
There's a wand?
Wait.
Is there an enemy in there?
Oh my god!
Bastard!
There it is!
Concentrated light, I told you.
Yo, that wand is...
kind of sick.
I will take that.
Thank you.
I like it.
Go up here.
Okay, so it is like...
Where is it located?
Bottom part of snowy depths.
Let's do this.
Snowy depths here.
So let's see how we can do this.
I'm guessing it's maybe like this high.
Then we have this area.
I'm just gonna make a...
Also, the line is a bit too thick, maybe.
Let's do something like this.
Magical temple.
Like right there.
Remove that.
And just connect these lines down here.
Now, it looks like...
Yeah, it actually looks like this.
And then, there's like this region.
In fact, I can do this better.
Remove this part.
Like that.
So you walk along, right?
And then at some point...
It's sort of...
How do I explain this?
Hold on, I need to see it.
Back.
I need to once again take a quick look at this.
So it goes like this.
And it opens up into this huge area.
And then it closes off again.
And what happens then?
Then it sort of continues here.
Ah, they do disappear!
Lovely!
Okay, awesome.
I actually like that.
I'm very happy about that.
I'm not happy about whatever's going on there.
How do I get through here now?
Oh, of course, I can just...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Mistakes were made.
Oh, I lost a bunch of HP.
Okay, so this leads into this area orb room.
And hopefully this does not spawn a boss, right?
I don't have a memory of that.
I don't think it does.
And it's like shaped like this.
Gotcha.
So that means it sort of does one of these.
And we have like an orb room.
Let's draw it something like...
I don't even know.
Hold on.
Maybe do straight lines.
Like this.
Actually a little further down, maybe.
So this is the orb room.
And then over here, it sort of goes up to this place.
I want to say like that.
It's very rough, of course, what I'm doing here.
Over there.
And actually, it goes more like this.
Like that, almost.
And over this part.
Wait, okay, so up here, we have like this weird triangle thingy.
Right.
Or like, it's actually a square.
Rotate at 45 degrees.
And inside of that, there's a little room.
I think it was square shaped.
Not entirely sure.
Something like that.
And inside of there, we have a note.
And a tablet.
The tablet.
Like that.
And we have one of these weird note thingies.
Let's put that in yellow.
Wait, how do I draw a note again?
How does that look in the game?
Right, like that.
Okay.
But it goes down.
That's that.
Like that.
Okay, neat.
And this is called the orb room.
And this whole area here is called, was it magical temple?
I think it was called magical temple.
Magical temple.
Okay.
This is very approximate.
Actually, it's not cool.
Yeah, this does look right, I think.
Except this part here.
Hold on.
I want to make this as accurate as I can, of course.
Oh, and things are shaking.
So it goes to here and then up.
Yep, I think I got it.
And then it stops here, goes to the right.
I just need to see where, how, oh, another invisible guy?
Okay, we're actually, we're actually dead almost.
We need to go.
Oh wait, is that a wand?
Did he have a wand on him?
I'm not sure if he did.
Don't think he did.
But it goes to here.
Okay, I think that's fine.
We made a good map.
A decent map.
Knockback on this is something else.
He got knocked into the fucking afterlife.
Okay, okay, okay.
I think it's time we move on.
36 HP.
No way, it's too risky.
Let's find a portal.
Oh shit.
What is that red thing?
Oh, sub dudes.
Let's be really careful.
Next.
Who else wants some?
Is anyone down here?
Okay, I think, I think we just go.
Yeah.
Go, go, go.
Lovely.
Okay, wands.
Let's see.
Uh, shuffle.
Ooh, hello.
Oh, is that a homing?
My prayers have been answered.
No way.
Oh, nice.
Yo, this is, this is great.
What's this?
Critical hit plus.
Peace with, okay.
Okay, here's the thing though.
Do I need that?
Now that I have this teleport wand, I feel like I can maybe skip on that.
Huh?
Hmm, I'm feeling frisky.
I think I'm going to skip on it.
I don't need it.
Okay, how much do things cost?
I have 1500.
Oh, nice.
Let's see what I want to get.
I would love to get that triple.
I don't have any triples or doubles for that matter.
I have nothing.
I think I want this wand and I want this wand.
The recharge time on this sucks.
It's really, oh, it also cast three spells per cast.
Hmm, but we have three rocks.
No, we have two rocks.
So, fuck it, I'm doing it.
Let's, let's try.
Nuke.
So wait.
I mean, that's a lot of damage, you know?
If I can get, okay, so a nuke.
I'm just wondering what kind of damage that is.
Is that mostly explosive?
I imagine.
I probably don't want to use it until I find explosive immunity, because I think this could go real bad.
Especially if it's homing, you know?
Let me put them down for now.
Maybe I don't want to nuke anything right now.
But I do want to do this.
Let's see it.
On your thing.
Is it not close enough?
Oh wow, that's real, that sucks.
That's really bad.
Why is it so bad?
Well, it works.
It works.
Okay, you know what?
Let me, let me do this.
Wait, fungal disease?
When near danger, you sprout?
No.
Glass cannon?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
A track, ooh, I don't like that either, man.
Shit, I don't like any of those.
But you know what?
I could come back later for some of these wands.
Hold on, I also had a great one, didn't I?
This one is kind of neat.
This has a very high mana charge speed.
I should be able to do something cool with that.
Let's think.
So basically, we need something that will usually produce a lot of...
Oh, it would cost a lot of mana, right?
What could that be?
Maybe that one.
Oh, 110 every time you shoot?
Maybe that's a bit too much.
Although, a classic with...
Hold on.
With a speed up?
Wait a minute.
Let's see this.
Oh, I don't have enough mana on this.
Let's get rid of that.
Oh, I don't have homing, of course.
I'm an idiot.
I'm dumb.
Man, this needs to be super close to work.
This feels like a lot worse than I remember.
Maybe this is not the exact same spell that I had.
Maybe this is a weaker version.
I don't like the sound this makes over here.
Wish I could just get rid of that.
You know what?
Let me reroll.
No, wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Hold on.
I'm not sure.
I want to buy one of these wands, I think.
I think I may want triplicate bolts.
Oh, no, no, no.
I want this maybe.
This is a good spell.
Oh, I don't even have money for that.
Never mind.
This is only 270.
That means I still have...
Oh, nice.
I still have 400 left then.
Let's get this one.
Triple spells, nice.
Let's throw this one over here.
So, actually not a bad wand either.
But I think I like the other one more.
One with the high mana charge speed.
You can probably do something crazy with that.
Only three slots though.
That's the thing.
That kind of sucks.
Yeah, it has a high recharge speed, unfortunately.
Castile is nice.
Is this even working on...
I feel like the Protectile modifier doesn't do shit for this one.
It does have a speed...
Okay, it does have a speed on it though.
And this one says speed times 2.5.
So, it's gotta work.
It's just, it's gotta...
Oh, hold on a second, dude.
Oh, we don't even need a triple, because this always shoots three spells per.
We can go a little nuts with that.
And put modifier on it, maybe.
What should we put on?
350 mana max.
This is... did I have enough mana for this at all?
100 mana?
110?
Yeah, I should have.
Yep, it works.
Let's try that, huh?
But I just wish it would go, like, further when I shoot it.
Ah, it is what it is.
No, I don't like that.
Am I boring?
I'm just gonna go with my glowing lance.
30 mana drain.
I can't, I can't, I can't see a good combination here.
I'm not seeing, I'm not seeing through the matrix code.
Something that makes sense.
But I definitely want speed up on that, than in that case.
Maybe a crit on this would be cool as well.
You know?
Would you spread?
Yeah, I'm not sure, man.
I guess I could add mana.
Depends how, hold on, how fast does this run empty?
Quite fast.
Why do that?
It's a modifier, it's only gonna modify...
Oh, this is the thing that's confusing, though.
Maybe it does make sense to have a triple here, then.
Because I want this modifier to affect both of these shots.
Does that work like that?
Wait a minute.
It's so confusing when it says spells per cast is three.
So that means it casts that one.
No, modify, modify, modifier, it casts that one.
And then, yeah, the triple is not necessary, I think.
Cast that one, that one, and then one more.
You know?
But it doesn't have one more, so.
I mean, not that you really need that, I guess, in this case.
I'm just gonna go with this.
And then I'm gonna come back here when I find more stuff and edit my shit.
That's the plan.
Oh, I need this.
There.
Let's go with that.
I like it.
Let's rock and roll.
And then I'm gonna re-roll these.
Saving grace.
Wait, what's this?
Gas... gases?
No.
Extra health.
Yo.
Okay, this one.
I think this one is...
Oh, man, they're both so good.
I think I want saving grace.
I'm taking it.
Fuck it.
I can't think forever.
I was debating whether or not I should come back later and grab the extra health thing when I have more base health.
But, you know, I could die in the Indian Terram there, so...
Oh, wait, I don't want to do that.
I want to teleport to the other side.
Okay, here we go.
Let's get ready.
Okay, so I teleport and then instantly I shoot rocks.
Teleport instantly rocks.
Here we go.
Oh, nice.
We're back, baby!
The rocks!
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm fucking stuck.
Okay, I just had an idea.
Long distance cast on the rock.
No, I like being able to teleport through walls, especially since we don't have any real digging, you know?
Hey, please die.
Oh, this is a mess.
Look, they lose focus.
This is terrible.
It is what it is, though.
It works.
It just needs to be a little closer.
Definitely works in a pinch here.
Yeah, I don't like these things.
Let's explode them.
What is that?
Doesn't that look like a steel statue of a detective?
With a boner?
The fuck?
Oh, wait, that was risky.
That's for you.
Oh, yo, what is this now?
Another one of these?
Okay, I'm not even sure this is the same run.
Is this the same run where we found a bunch of bottles?
Or was it the one before?
The hell?
How do I even...
That's the risk doing this sort of thing.
It's risky.
Oh, wait, is that thing gonna explode in the acid?
Oh, you know what?
Holy shit.
Rock, my old friend.
Wait, plastic?
Say what?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait a second here.
Let me gently put this down.
Wait, is this not a potion?
I thought...
Oh, wait, what?
Oh, wait, I can't pick...
Oh, I can't pick them up.
I can pick this one up, whiskey.
Oh my god, it's a bar.
Look at the cocktail symbol.
I love Heezy people.
They're so Heezy going, you know?
Heezy to talk to, so nice.
I love these rocks.
Damn.
Mario.
What is that?
Oh, Akiva Skibi.
And, dude, we have a broken wand as well.
Good times.
Now we just gotta find the anvil.
Oh, wait a minute.
Is this?
Ah, ha, ha.
Bomb?
What's this?
Venomous curse, red glimmer.
Wait.
Ha.
That's the same thing we found in the lake house.
Turn it all to water.
Fortunately, I don't have a good mixing wand.
Catalina wine mixer.
That's what I need right now.
Important stuff, the Catalina wine mixer.
Okay, oh, wait, we can teleport through.
Do I want to just teleport through, though?
Is that...
Looks like a bad idea.
Okay, fuck it.
Oh, come on, rocks.
Come on, rocks.
Do you think rocks?
Okay, actually, we didn't lose that much HP.
Is this going really, really well here?
My god, the rock is the best spell in the game.
It's so good.
Look at this shit.
Why is there so much money?
Hey.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Just slam this body into the side of that steel wall.
All his bones fucking crushed to dust.
Ah, here it is.
Wait, is this always the bottom right?
I feel like I've already seen it here.
Oh.
Goddammit, it says shuffle wand.
Blood mist.
A cloud of blood mist.
Wait, weakening curse.
Target hit by a projectile takes 25% extra melee damage for a time.
I don't like any of this.
Am I crazy?
This all sucks ass.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Okay, hands to test.
Uh-oh.
It's honestly, the rock is also one of the funniest spells.
It's just so entertaining to kill enemies with a rock.
Oh, man, there's so many of these propane tanks.
Come on, come closer to the rock.
You know what, I should get rid of these.
Damn.
That was a crazy chain reaction.
There we go.
Everything died.
Hey, what the hell's going on here?
What is this place?
God, I love this level.
It's the best level in...
Oh!
Best level in the game.
Makes it...
Ah, it doesn't matter.
Actually, it doesn't matter.
It's crazy that I can just go through walls.
It's completely unprecedented.
1300 gold already.
I can already go back and buy some of the ones that I missed.
But not yet.
Actually, I'm here anyway.
Fuck it!
Oh, wait, I need to...
Let's not forget about this.
There we go.
So cool.
All right.
I kind of want this.
Reduce recharge.
Reduce...
Recharge.
Nice.
And I don't care for the other ones.
I really don't.
Is the wand any good?
Sort of.
Not the worst wand.
Man, is this the first time I've had all no-shuffle wands?
I just noticed.
Not bad.
What should I put on this one?
Reduce recharge.
You know what?
Wait, I fucked this up.
Is this...
This should be better, right?
I can try it, I guess.
Yeah, that's fine.
Uh, what else should I be doing?
Should I do anything else?
I can buy that.
I kind of want to buy these.
They seem nice.
I don't have enough money, though.
Something is exploding here.
Wait, wait, I have an idea.
Let's go in the water pool and teleport through.
Oh, it's not far enough.
Or it's not close enough, I mean.
Dang it!
Okay.
That's fine.
Man, this rock is just eager as hell.
Get his hands on that statue.
Hey!
Sup?
There's a wand right here.
Wow.
Damn!
800 mana charge.
Cast two spells per cast, though.
Eh.
Not the biggest fan of that.
But I think I may like it.
As a wand?
Could be cool.
What?
That was close!
I almost went in there!
That's the risk.
Man, I wish I had all seeing eye.
Oh, shit.
Oh, wow.
Why did I drop so much gold?
I don't understand.
If you die, I'm gonna have more than one at you.
Yeah.
Dude, this is gonna be insane if I can get...
Oh, dude.
If I can get healing bolts and make it work.
Imagine every time I'm about...
I actually die, I just heal up again and I go again.
That is nuts.
My rocks are too strong.
Eh.
Ah, damn it.
4000 damage I just did.
And there we go.
What is this thing?
Looks like some kind of tube they put people inside.
What else?
I want to find more hearts.
There we go.
And then they take care of the rest.
Beautiful stuff.
Ha ha ha.
I can't get enough.
Come on.
Explode that thing, please.
There we go.
It's like the safety thing.
As soon as I transport to the other side, make a couple rocks.
Sure.
Oh.
Damn.
I'm a menace.
I cannot be stopped.
When I have rocks, I'm invincible.
Oh shit, I'm stuck.
Good thing we have that.
My hand is so itchy.
Okay.
No, I almost teleported in there.
I would have been a disaster.
Good.
I'm scared of electricity so much.
Man, I...
Okay, hold on.
I need to get in there.
There's a party going on and I'm not invited.
Makes me unhappy.
Okay, it's just toxic sludge.
Oh.
Teleportation.
Why is there that there?
Oh, that's a big container of it too.
Ooh, interesting.
Can I somehow get in there?
Too much fire, man.
Whoa.
I love kicking the rocks and then they start to home.
That's the best feeling in the world.
All right, there we go, there we go.
Nice.
Okay.
That's very fiery.
Anything in here?
I feel like there's something down there.
There was something down there.
There's just gonna be rocks all over these levels.
Especially because I summon two at a time.
I think I've been here before.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Not here though.
Aha!
What is this?
Energy orb.
That's not a bad wand!
Oh, it's spells per cast too.
I hate that.
Maybe I like it more than this one though.
Yeah, why not?
Oh, it digs.
Oh, that's actually nice.
That's actually really nice.
It's nice for those snowy parts.
Bam, bam, bam.
Oh, that's electric.
Look at that shit.
That's a hazard.
It's gone now.
Hello!
My rock is stuck on me.
Right in the tummy.
Yellow!
Come on, rocks, do your thing.
Weird fungus pouch.
Huh?
Can I get high?
Wait a minute.
Oh my god!
I bought a bag of fungus!
Dude, we're getting high.
Oh yeah, boy.
Oh, we're tripping balls.
Are we?
Not yet.
We're just tripping some.
Oh, make a lot of mushrooms.
Make all the mushrooms.
Oh yeah.
Consume that shit.
Oh, that's right.
Heavily tripping.
Okay, we're not quite there yet.
I'm gonna make a whole fucking mountain of fungus.
It's happening.
Grow those fungi.
Eat it.
Eat it all.
All of it.
Come on.
Now?
Heavily tripping.
Not quite yet.
How much do we need, man?
Tripping balls.
More.
Ball!
Weird fungus shifting in colors.
What?
Wait, did I just...
Huh?
Wait a minute.
So, weird fungus.
Oh my god.
Weird fungus has become lava?
You're kidding.
All over?
Okay.
I don't know if I like that.
I gotta be honest here.
That...
Yeah, that doesn't feel good.
I feel like that's bad.
This is a bad situation.
I wonder what fungus land looks like.
Maybe I don't want to know.
What the hell?
What are the chances as well?
Like...
You know?
I was tripping on some fungus and then that's what's changing.
Cool though.
I swear to god, the kick is actually insane.
The damage from that when you kick certain things, you know?
It's pretty good.
Ah!
A chest!
Hidden in some toxic sludge.
Uh...
Odd f- No.
No.
Nope.
Thanks though.
I appreciate it, but no thanks.
Okay, we're actually at the portal.
And we are relatively low HP.
Maybe it is time to...
You know, GTFO.
Rotten meat.
Kinda want to eat it.
Kinda also don't want to eat it, you know?
Come on, Rock!
Get him!
Very good.
Lovely.
What's happening here?
Water!
Oh!
Whoa!
I'm low HP.
I'm very close to going to the portal.
Not quite there yet though, mentally, but almost.
I'm very close.
To just saying, fuck it.
And move on.
I am curious about this.
Hold on.
There's gotta be a chest or something there.
Like, that is such a huge collection of teleportation.
Why is it there?
Is there a puzzle maybe?
Somehow.
Look, look how large that is.
Why is the music so relaxing?
Man, I'm tempted to teleport into the teleportation.
Is that crazy?
No, I'm not gonna do it.
Things could go heavily wrong if I do that.
Yeah, let's not do that.
If I had a plasma beam, I would definitely get in there.
But I don't.
Wow, the rocks can't crit.
It's confirmed.
I wasn't sure about that.
Man, what are the...
These guys are so weird.
They seem passive almost.
Like, I always kill them, but they always seem a little...
Weird.
Just murder all of them.
Change all this.
Kill that guy.
Get his money.
Thank you very much.
Let me rock your world.
I love these one-liners.
Uh, I can dig.
Actually insanely effective against snow.
This weapon here, this is good stuff.
I really should be going.
I really should get out of here.
I don't know why I'm squeezing the lemon.
All right, fuck it.
Let's go.
No more squeezing.
Sweet.
Okay, what do we got?
Bouncing, burst.
Always cast.
Is that saw blades?
Rotating saw blades.
Whoa!
A bunch of shit.
And some of them good.
What's that?
Naded.
No more knockback.
Lukey minion.
Iron stomach.
I don't like any of that.
I mean, I say that because I don't really know what this exactly does.
Like, okay, I don't suffer any negative effects of eating.
Okay, cool.
Oh, you mean like...
Wait, are you saying I can't trip anymore?
Unless tripping is not considered a negative effect.
It could be considered a positive effect.
I don't know.
I would like to reroll.
Rage, fueled levitation.
Ooh.
Hello.
Oh!
Oh, I'm so tempted.
I'm tempted.
I don't know.
This one or that one?
Oh, why do I have to do that?
Why do I have to make such a hard choice?
Hold on, we still have...
How many holy mountains do we have left?
There's...
Hold on, we just came from...
Heezy base.
There's at least three more...
Yeah, this is worth it.
We're taking that.
Taking that, baby.
The extra perk.
Yes, sir.
I don't think this is retroactive.
I don't think we can go back and find...
Because that's from now on, right?
I want this one, obviously.
Obviously.
Is that explosion on slimy enemies?
Fireball orbit.
Makes four fireballs rotate around a projectile.
Dude.
This one, though.
I like this one!
That's a good one right there.
And a firebolt with...
Oh, and we have infinite, right?
Oh, man.
And that...
Electric?
I don't know.
I don't like...
I hate this sort of stuff, because it can kill me if I'm not careful.
You know, it's bad.
Frozen charge.
That could be cool.
Let's drop a bunch of...
Also, is this one any good?
No, spells per cast seven?
Yikes.
Let's put those here for now, though.
Yeah, this one sucks.
This wand is actually good...
Sort of good.
Wait, wait, wait.
Spells per cast...
What is with these spells per cast five and six and all that bullshit?
I don't want...
Can I just get a simple one?
No!
Let's shuffle!
Man.
I guess I'll take this.
And get rid of some of these energy orbs.
Unless...
Maybe I want to go with firebolts.
I want to use this.
I want to make a wand out of that.
That's basically what I'm aiming for right now.
I want that real bad.
And we're going to make something.
Maybe with the triplicate bolt.
Imagine that.
Oh, but wait.
These do reflect sometimes and come back to me.
So that's a no bueno.
We need a spell that doesn't bounce.
Does this bounce?
Oh, wait.
These are the big ones, right?
I don't think it bounces.
No.
But the issue is, if this gets reflected, say, on the shield and comes back at me, then I'm fucked.
But maybe they already did damage me.
I don't know.
So they do 11 damage right now.
I wish I had a spark bolt right now.
That would be great.
Is there one on these?
No, these bounce.
That's bad.
That will kill me.
We don't want bounce.
We want as little bounce as possible.
Maybe energy sphere is the way to go.
But they also bounce, right?
Hold on.
Yeah, they bounce.
They bounce for show.
What should I do?
Is it just triplicate bolt time?
I kind of like the energy orb as a base here.
There's just too many of them.
Let me get rid of some.
That should be okay.
So let's see what we can do.
Speed up.
This one.
It casts two spells per cast.
Let's remember that.
So it should be doing this now?
Yes.
That's actually nuts.
The speed up makes this great.
And hold on.
This has...
These add spread.
Okay, interesting.
So if I do this...
Much better.
Not bad at all.
It looks cool too!
That's important, of course.
It has to look cool.
Very important.
Speed up.
Extra damage.
Oh, this is gonna do a lot of damage.
So maybe if we do a triple.
That may be too much already.
Hold on.
Let's see.
Two spells.
This one.
One, two, three.
And then it casts another spell.
That's pretty fast.
But...
Hold on a second.
No.
Okay.
Let's think.
What is limiting this right now?
It's the recharge.
So we add this to it.
So maybe we get rid of one of these.
And maybe we do that.
Here, here, here.
Reduce recharge time.
Oh yeah, that's the shit right there.
Ooh, that's nice.
That's really cool.
Is that faster?
I can't tell.
Dum, dum, dum.
No, this is...
So look, it's faster without the chainsaw now.
But if we did something like this, there's a difference.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
Oh, it's weird how that works, isn't it?
It's really weird.
Hold on, what if we do that?
Hold on a second.
We gotta, we gotta...
Okay.
Oh, I need one more slot.
That's all I need.
One more slot, that would have been great.
Uh, hold on.
Oh, this actually adds a lot of spread, too.
Maybe we get rid of the speed, because I want to add mana to this.
And then, uh, we add this.
Yo, that's fucking crazy.
Now I'm...
Dude.
That is nuts!
Hold on.
Is this scary?
Holy fuck!
Okay, we gotta go with that.
We gotta go with that!
Holy...
I made a sick want!
That
is crazy.
Damn.
Let's try something here.
Let's add a bunch of speed.
Is this actually gonna affect this?
It's not.
Not really.
I want to be able to launch this with more...
You know?
I cannot...
Any of this?
Whatever.
Unless we do that?
Wait.
This is starting to piss me off.
We need to...
Delete these rocks.
Hahahaha!
Look at the recoil on this!
This is... the recoil is maybe actually a problem.
We have to be ultra careful with the recoil.
Oh, man.
This right here is nuts.
Wow.
And you know what else?
If we were to add a digging bolt...
Hold on.
Let me actually test something.
What if we remove the chainsaw?
Oh, yeah.
This is totally what's making this happen right now.
So I don't quite understand how exactly this fucking works.
It just works, you know?
Sometimes I swap things around, experiment.
It's basically trial and error, most of this.
Because I don't understand this one very much.
I don't understand how reducing recharge time by 0.17 can take something from this.
So, this.
That is not a 0.17 seconds of difference.
It's just not.
It's not.
I don't get it.
Hold on.
Okay, so changing the order of these doesn't do anything, it seems.
That statue has seen better...
Wait, am I actually digging through this?
Wow.
I have a crazy wand.
What should I put on the last wand?
Do I even need anything there?
Oh, dude, I have an idea.
Dude.
What if we were to do freeze charge on the rocks?
Oh, that looks messed up.
Frozen charge.
Oh, wait, it never releases it because it hasn't impacted anything or...
Oh, wait, it's all frozen now.
Oh, no, no, I don't like that.
I don't like that.
Nope, we're not doing that.
It was cool in practice or in theory, I mean.
But that's all about it.
I think this is fine.
We don't need to speed up on this because, honestly, it didn't seem to do anything.
So we're going to save these speed ups.
Speed ups are saved.
Okay.
I think it's time to get the fuck out of here.
This is awesome.
And we got to teleport.
Here we go.
It's underground jungle time.
Oh, wait, weird fungus is now lava.
This is the fungus place.
Wait, this is slime.
That's fine.
A double spirit bolt magic missile.
Bro, that is a...
Is that not a sick wand?
Hold on a fucking second.
Wait a minute.
Oh, look at lava.
Oh, no, I have bad feelings about this.
I have really bad feelings about this.
Let me do this.
Do that.
And the double is actually something I can keep.
Let's do this one.
Here and that one.
Ah, damn it.
I can't move all that way.
Stack this one on the other one.
Put this one somewhere.
This holy mountain looks like trash because of what I've done to it.
I want to move this down there, basically.
But hold on, maybe with that mana charge speed, we don't really need to have plus mana.
Let's see what this feels.
Also, this is now only spells per cast one.
Oh, interesting.
Wait.
I'm limited by recharge, I think.
Wait, recharge is 0.42, 0.07.
Wait a minute.
Okay, that's already better.
That act, that's sustained too.
Oh, but look at how they fly down.
That scares me a little bit.
Like, if I shoot straight up like this, will it not just land on me?
No, it's at an angle, it seems.
Okay, hmm.
Maybe it's fine.
Let me see the damage here.
It's not as fast as the other one.
It's good damage, man.
It's good damage.
You know, it's good.
Why does that...
Wow.
Oh, we actually go oom.
I thought we were limited by recharge.
We're limited by mana in this case.
So hold on.
Do we need this?
Oh, yeah, we need it.
That is too crazy.
I think I like the first one more.
We got to put it up here.
This is the way.
At least right now.
Maybe on this one, we can put the rocks.
Hmm.
This seems crazy, though.
I feel like I should...
I can utilize this in some crazy fashion.
Ah, I wish I had spark bolts.
Those would slap with the bloodlust.
Right?
I mean, this is for sure the way to go.
Hold on.
It has two spells per cast.
So it's going modify...
This is all modifiers.
So one spell.
And this spell contains three spells, which is that one, that one.
And one more, which is that one.
But then it's spells per cast two.
Is that what's doing it?
I'm actually not sure.
If I were to just take these without the chainsaw.
Super slow.
Crazy how I need all of these, right?
I like the...
I like this.
This...
Somehow we made something happen here.
And I'm not quite sure how we did it, but we did it.
This one is sick.
I like it.
Let's put it...
Let's put these on here.
Could also remove this wand, I guess.
Replace it.
No, no, no.
This is the...
Of course we need this one.
We need this one, because this is the homing.
Obviously, it's not going to work on the other one.
Come on, man.
Think.
The last one.
I'm not sure what to put on there.
Maybe nothing for now.
Let's leave it empty.
I do like having...
Maybe we can do this.
Yeah.
Nah.
That one.
That can dig, I guess.
Wait, what was the digging one?
This one.
Maybe I just want that.
No, this is the small one.
I need the big one, big one.
Big one.
Yeah, sure.
Let's go with that.
We have a digging wand.
Off we go.
I'm afraid of the lava, dude.
I really am.
Oh, nice.
Wait, was there a heart and a wand?
The hell?
I thought there could only be one thing in these.
Kind of want speed up on this now that I look at it.
The drop-off is a bit too much for me.
Am I crazy?
I mean, we're gonna find a better wand, and then we're gonna slap this thing on, you know?
And we still have rocks, too.
1100 mana.
Dude, there are so many wands.
Damn.
I need to find a lot of hearts.
I feel like the only limiting factor now is not my damage on, like, last big run we had.
Now it's HP.
Man, they die quick.
This is a great wand.
And hold on, there's also a boss here, right?
Let's go fuck that guy up.
We have crazy wand.
And the recoil is nuts.
Reminds me of that similar wand I made some time ago, where I also got shot into the heaven every time I shot my shot, you know?
That's in here.
I needed water anyway.
Oh, that's burning.
I'm being a little risky here with my teleports.
Wait a minute.
Did it bleed weird fungus, which made all this into fire?
I think that's what's happening here.
Oh, God.
I just lost a shit ton of HP.
I need speed up on this bad.
I have no range.
Like, call me crazy, but the wand is maybe too powerful.
Maybe I do want to tone it down a bit and gain that extra speed instead.
Oh, God.
I hate the way they just appear out of nowhere with their legs.
Oh, where did that guy come from?
See this, the way they fall down.
That's what happens when you don't have speed.
What's happening?
Are these things spawning?
Is that guy shooting a gun that shoots spiders?
No fucking way.
That's what it feels like.
Where did he go?
That's right.
Stay mad.
See, all these falling projectiles could have killed me.
Fuck off.
The next thing we need is to find a healing spell.
Oh, not bad.
Not bad at all.
I'll take it.
I'll take it back to base.
Back to the collection.
Back to the lab again.
Oh, there goes gravity.
Uh...
I just need to click my button once and people die.
I don't need to hold it at all.
Wait a minute, didn't I see something up here?
I did.
Don't you bleed lava on me?
Okay.
Yo, that's a sick wand.
Decent amount of mana max and a lot of mana charge speed.
With a lot of slots.
Hello?
Wait a minute.
So this one has point...
This could be sick.
This could be really nice.
Right?
If I put this stuff on this one, I even have more slots so I can add speed up and all that.
Oh, man.
Okay, I'm coming back for this.
Uh, hello, guys.
Oh, I think I almost just killed myself there.
And look, there's lava here.
That's bad.
What is this now?
LARP?
A projectile would shoot out eight copies of itself when it expires or hits the ground.
Okay.
It's shuffled, though.
Jesus fuck, there's a lot of slots on this one.
So let's remember, here I go right.
And right again.
And this is next to that wand and we're at the entrance.
I know how to get back.
Now, you know what, let's...
This lava will fuck me later.
I know it.
Okay.
This puts...
Wait, is there a guy in here?
It's not that...
Like, I heard something.
Okay, uh, the rest I don't care for.
Get rid of the wand.
Now we go grab that other wand.
Down here.
This guy shoots mines.
Can't have that.
Oh, wow.
The power on this is unprecedented.
It's wild.
Is that the wand?
No.
Wait, where did I find it?
Wait, is it?
No, this is not the...
This is the one I left behind, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Where was that wand?
I'm already lost.
No, it wasn't down there.
It was somewhere up here, I think.
So I dropped that wand.
And then I went more this way.
I went like here.
And I went up.
I think I went...
Is it that one?
It is.
Good.
There's even another wand here.
Dude.
I think he died.
Add mana.
Luminous boomerang.
Return.
Holy shit.
There's a lot of crap on this.
I'm coming back for that one too.
This is a fucking wand, pinata.
But first we gotta make a sick wand.
Out of what we have here.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's do this now.
Oh, wait.
And then at the front, that.
Let's see.
Wait, wait, wait.
I need more distance.
Oh, it's so much better.
It's so much better.
Damn.
Oh, it's scary though.
Oh, I'm scared of the triplicate still though.
It's scary.
It scares me.
Like look at it, man.
Look at that shit.
How does that not scare you?
Do I need this?
Yo, maybe I don't even need it.
Hold on.
What if I do it even faster?
This is just like insanity.
Hold on, we can also try another mana.
But we're not limited by mana now.
We're limited by...
Recharge, actually.
Right?
If I remove this, what happens then?
Oh, it sucks.
But if I add this one...
Wait.
Wait, so...
0.33.
Oh, shit.
So I'm actually...
I'm limited by cast delay now.
Yes.
So let's see.
This adds 0.13 cast delay.
What else?
This also adds cast delay.
This one removes some.
Did I have an extra one of those?
I don't think so.
Maybe we don't need that actually.
Hold on.
This also adds a bunch of cast delay.
But the...
But this one...
Only removes recharge time.
But obviously it does more than that.
Also, it does say it has some magical properties.
So whatever the fuck that even means, right?
Oh, well.
It works.
I'm running with that, baby.
It's a superior version of this wand, basically.
And then I want to go back and exchange this wand for the other one we found.
Dude, this is just like insane.
We get all the things.
Now I just need to not die.
I'm actually kind of low on HP.
This is like the thing.
I need healing.
Need to find healing.
Healing spell.
There we are.
We also kill that thing.
Actually, worm blood.
Let's grab some of that.
Get rid of the whiskey.
I'm gonna pick up a bunch of worm blood.
I think it's just nice to have.
Come on.
Nice.
Oh, look at all that worm blood.
Oh, yeah.
Fill me up.
Oh, that's a lot.
Look at that.
We are ready for any dark region.
We have water.
We have that.
We have music.
Okay.
Let's play this slow and careful now, given our lack of HP.
I'm less scared of falling projectiles now, because they shoot so fast.
Wait, is that...
Yo, the digging on this is actually pretty sweet.
Ah, here we go.
Here we go.
The dragon cave.
You know what?
We should put that on the map.
Let's see exactly where this is.
Relative to the bottom.
Hold on.
Thanks.
There's a guy over there.
Jesus Christ, the recoil.
Is that the bottom?
I think it's closer to the bottom than the top.
Let's just say that.
Let's see how it's shaped.
It's like a...
Okay.
All right.
Seems feasible.
Let's see here.
Easy base.
Underground jungle.
This is where we are now.
Somewhere on this side, maybe like...
I want to say...
Hold on.
More like this.
Let's say there.
It sort of does a...
I'm gonna make it a little bit nice looking here.
Maybe proportions are a little bit off here.
And then there's a huge fucking egg.
Just sitting there.
And this is the...
Dragon Cave.
Cool.
Probably this should be much smaller.
Actually, you know what?
Let's resize this a bit.
Oh, damn it.
Really?
Hold on.
Let's say that is the more appropriate size.
I think that makes more sense.
It's really not that big, you know?
Draw a line here.
There we go.
Save that.
Add it to the list.
Okay.
Let's fuck this guy up, huh?
I think we can pretty much one-shot this guy with what we've got here.
So...
Let's mess up his day.
Oh, my god.
The recoil.
I need to stand up against something.
Maybe up here.
Oh, wait.
I can't really dig very effectively here.
Maybe I cannot get in.
It's gonna take forever.
Maybe I just need to reach a certain point in the center and then he will pop.
Ah, shit.
I'm not so sure, actually.
I don't want to stand too close, either.
I'm scared.
You know what?
I have an idea.
Let's...
Is there a place I can stand without getting pushed so...
It doesn't look like it.
I'm gonna dig to the center.
Maybe that's enough.
The good thing about the recoil is that when I shoot, at least I won't accidentally hit my own beam of projectiles because I get thrown back.
Wanna do it?
Spawn.
Do your thing.
I think you have to destroy a certain percentage area-wise of this egg and that triggers his spawn.
That's what it felt like in the past, at least.
Come on, now.
Come out to play!
Looks like a menacing mouth right now, doesn't it?
Slowly but surely.
He's just gonna pop suddenly and I'm gonna get a fright.
Maybe if I stand here for a bit.
I don't want to be too close.
Come on!
I have a feeling it's any second now.
Gotta scratch my nose.
Oh, man.
Is this a bit too risky?
I have 100 HP.
Wait a minute.
No, it's not.
I believe.
Wait, do I need to get closer?
What was that?
Something like a blowpipe.
Oh, blow dart sound.
Come on!
Yeah, okay, okay.
You gotta get close.
Oh, he's dead.
I fucked you up, bitch.
Yep, there it is.
Gossip HP.
Nice, nice, nice, nice.
Whoa!
Yo, that wand slaps.
Thank you.
What's this?
Sawblade orbit?
Right.
Well, that was cool.
Got him.
Next.
It says something when I don't even use my rocks anymore.
How effective this new wand I made is.
And the rocks themselves are insane.
I'm so slimy.
I'm 100% slimy.
Get that off of me.
There we go.
The digging is actually decent.
Oh!
Fuck, you scared me.
Oh, shit.
Get the fuck out of dodge.
This wand is actually nice to get out of sticky situations because it just goes through walls, you know, like that.
Very nice.
Oh, I'm so slimy.
Holy shit.
Dude, it's my game.
Feels like my game is lagging right now.
Am I crazy?
Maybe it's just a slime making me think that.
Get rid of the slime.
What do we got?
That is a lot of blood.
Let me go.
Okay, I thought for a second it was gonna eat me.
I'm tempted to go through.
Should I go?
Oh, wait, wait, no, no.
Before we go through, we got to go back to the holy mountain up top.
Just to see exactly what we left behind.
Because there's a lot of spells there.
Just need to take a look, you know?
Hello?
There's something going on up there.
By the way, I think I know how to defeat the boss in the ancient laboratory.
The trick is to have something that does a lot of damage in a short amount of time.
Because whenever his shield is down is when you have to hit him, right?
I think this one will do wonders.
Because it does an insane amount of damage in no time.
Lava to blood!
Okay!
That sounds cool as hell!
I almost want to take that.
Maybe I'll...
I'm gonna go upstairs anyway right now.
And then I'm gonna come back for that.
Because what I'm thinking...
If all the weird fungus is lava...
That's what scares me right now.
You know?
So if I can turn that into blood on command...
Hey!
I'll be pretty deep!
I don't know why I just said that would be pretty deep.
As if that's a normal expression to make when you say something is very cool.
I don't know what's wrong.
Uh, that's the...
Here we are.
Okay!
Let's see.
What should we not leave on the table before we go?
Maybe I'll...
Okay, so these things...
Cost 70 mana.
I'm scared of trying them.
I think I tried one of these before and it was okay-ish.
But it wasn't like anything crazy.
Uh...
Hmm.
Oh, wait a minute!
Why do I not just transfer...
Hold on.
Is this not just better?
I have more slot.
Wait, is this...
Okay, it's not.
It's not...
What's the big difference?
Recharge time.
We're limited on recharge time.
What can we use to reduce...
This one, actually.
If we...
If we put that at the end...
That could have gone so bad!
I didn't even think about it.
Why did I even do this?
That was such a bad thing to do.
Because these projectiles can hit me.
And damage me because of bloodlust.
Stop doing that, Oliver.
Maniac.
Recharge time.
Recharge...
What?
Does anything...
Reduce recharge time.
Let's see here.
What do we have?
Oh wait, we don't have any spells over there.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
Can we make this work somehow?
How much is this damage?
Oh, this is so broken it won't...
It's not gonna tell me.
I mean, it's not gonna be as good as the other one, obviously.
But maybe it's gonna be good enough.
No, I don't like it.
I don't like it.
Let me think.
One, two...
Ah man, I just wish...
Okay, whatever.
Back to this configuration.
It's too good.
But maybe we'll try something...
I'll leave some of these here.
Use one of them up there.
Maybe I'll quickly try just to remind myself.
Oh, hold on, hold on.
So I'm in three short-range electrical orbs.
You know what, just to be safe.
Right, okay, so that's how that works.
Yeah, that's pretty cool.
We can bring one of those with us.
Light is good, I think.
No, maybe we don't need light anymore because we have worm blood.
Leave that here.
Maybe you don't need all of these energy orbs either.
Okay, seems good.
What was this one?
Explosion on slimy enemies.
That actually...
And that one as well I want.
That could be cool, you know?
Given all the slime stuff, especially in this area.
Okay, I don't think I want anything else from here.
Maybe that one.
Maybe.
Okay, let's slowly head out of here.
I'm gonna explore on the way down in a new direction, and then we're gonna make our way out of here.
That's the plan.
I want to fly downwards.
Is that... why would I do that?
Oh, it does add projectile speed, I guess.
Eh.
No, thanks.
Wait, wait, wait.
Murder everything before anyone has a chance to kill you.
Look at all the gold I'm getting.
Oh, that's a mine.
Bye-bye.
This may be the most powerful wand I've ever made.
I think it is.
I've never done this amount of damage before, in such a short amount of time.
Let's rock and roll.
Wait with the healing, just in case.
Okay, what do we have here?
Remove bounce.
Dude, I don't like any of these spells.
Oh, but we get an extra perk, that's right.
Melee immunity?
Uh, oh, is it time?
Teleport time.
You take 20% less damage, you teleport away.
That sounds terrible.
Kind of want melee immunity.
But I also kind of want to be a little greedy here and not take this perk until later and come back.
Is that crazy?
Oh, man.
Wand radar?
That sounds terrible, because you can sort of see why there's a wand anyway through the wall, right?
Melee immunity was really cool, though.
I had that once before.
Actually completely eliminated the threat of the spiders, which is something I actually really like.
And other enemies as well, I guess.
The kicking guy.
I'm gonna take it.
Oh, wait, wait, am I though?
Yeah, I'm gonna take it.
I'm taking it.
And then, I don't think I'm gonna do anything else in here, because I don't want to buy any of this.
This all sucks.
I'm gonna heal.
325 HP.
If we took the 50%, I mean, we would have been at 470 something, right?
Not really anything game breaking there or game changing.
So I think I've made the right choice.
Do I want anything on this wand at all?
Anything?
No.
Nope.
We have arrived at the vault.
Also, it's soon time.
Oh, but hold on a second.
I just realized, how the fuck are we gonna get back to the surface without angering the gods?
Oh, I should have taken the piece with the gods when I had the chance.
I didn't think about this.
Wait, what the hell is that animal?
Look at that.
What the hell?
I don't think I've ever seen that.
All right, let's take it easy here.
Take it easy.
I am oily and there's fire.
Bad combo.
Whoa.
Oh, come on, guys.
Stop it.
Ah, you bastard.
Threw a mine on me.
Exploded right in my face.
I really want fire immunity, like real bad.
What?
Okay, well, I guess that's it anyway.
The gods have been angered.
Is he gonna appear here now or something?
Oh, wait, that's probably a worm.
It wasn't me.
Yeah, it's gotta be.
Well, rip.
That's that, I guess.
I mean, we can probably kill them, right?
We have sick DPS.
Maybe the gods are not an issue.
Maybe they should be a...
Oh, man.
But are they only gonna appear in the mountain?
What if I go back now?
That's my question.
Come here.
Man, I'm tempted to go back and test.
Just, you know, I'm going back.
I need to see...
I need to get this over...
I need to get this over with immediately.
I can't have this hanging over my head.
Come on.
Am I crazy or do everyone drop way more gold than usual?
I feel like...
Maybe just because I'm later in the game, but...
Ah, here we go.
Okay, wait, I know the rocks are really good.
But let me try my wand.
Well...
Okay.
It's not an issue.
We're good.
It's actually not an issue.
Never...
Hello?
The fuck?
Oh, you know what happened?
The spiders dug their way in here.
And that's what angered the gods.
Right?
Wait, how did they get in?
What is this again?
Worm crystal.
I'm actually not sure what that is.
Wait, where did they get in?
Over here?
Hold on, can I?
Ah, it's not quite far enough.
Close enough.
Ah, okay, okay, okay.
Dude, that's amazing!
That means I can get up here!
That's all I wanted!
Fuck yeah!
Unbelievable.
You know what?
Do I have any digging?
No, I don't actually have any real digging.
I can't go up yet.
No, no, no, don't go back yet.
Don't go back yet.
I need to find a plasma cutter or similar.
And then I go back up.
That's the condition.
So that's actually our mission right now.
Find a plasma cutter.
Or something that digs through the hardest of...
What the fuck just happened with the blood?
The blood just multiplied.
You see that?
Interesting stuff there.
Why does it feel like the game is lagging?
Oh my lord.
Oh, the game is lagging?
What the fuck?
Whoa, it's low motion!
Why is it so slow?
What is happening?
Infestation?
What is going on?
A bunch of magical sparks that fly in every direction.
I'm super curious about this.
I'm scared of it though.
Should I try it?
Fuck it.
Let's try it.
Oh, that hurts me!
Man, it is...
The game is like insanely slow.
Why is this happening?
What the...
Hold on.
I have a...
I'm gonna try and restart.
This doesn't feel right.
Something's off.
This game is completely fucked right now.
Like, it's unplayable.
What is happening?
Let's see.
Oh my god, it's still slow.
Why is it like this?
I've never had this.
There's a wand there.
Damn it!
You got a shot off on me.
Whoa, intense concentrated light.
Toxic sludge to acid.
Formation pentagon.
Let's try it.
Whoa!
Why does that look like that?
That was a pretty pattern.
One...
One ten man...
Okay.
Interesting.
Oh, hello there.
Bye-bye.
I think just a bunch of shit happened on screen, and the game just couldn't keep up.
Glimmer.
Giant spirit bolt.
Dude, why are there...
I'm getting showered with wands in this run.
It's...
Look at that!
It's everywhere.
Not complaining though.
Oh wait, I can...
Get in there.
Wait, what?
A slow orb of void that eats through all obstacles and casts another spell as it expires.
Yo, isn't this gonna make an insanely...
Hold on, it's random?
Let's try it.
Oh god.
What did I just take damage from?
Holy shit.
Wait, how many did it...
Oh, so it's using up multiple...
Okay, I see, I see.
That is insane digging.
I mean, I have a lot of them at my disposal.
I think I just found my way up.
Guys, that's it.
We fight...
Wait, let's take it out of here.
This is it, man.
Hold on, do I want to go out yet?
Or should I go to the next holy mountain just to see the perks?
Oh man, I'm gonna go see the perks.
Yeah, let's keep exploring.
We're not done here yet.
No, no, no.
We need more HP as well.
We need to find hearts.
That's the name of the game right now.
Wow, what's going on in there?
Imagine turning toxic sluts into water with eating fungus.
I can get in there.
Oh wait, electricity.
Show it.
Could I be afraid?
Holy shit.
I should be a little afraid at least here.
And that thing as well is scaring.
Uh oh.
Oh!
Jesus.
I'm stuck, I'm stuck.
That's the nice thing about this teleport wand.
If you're stuck, you just use it and you're not stuck anymore.
Holy fucking shit.
Another one.
Can I stag it?
Oh, freezing gaze!
I love that one!
Dude!
We're going back.
We need to immediately try this.
Oh, but wait a minute.
Can we even do anything now that we angered the...
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shit.
Oh wait, this is an issue.
Can we ever change wands now?
Oh wait, wait, wait.
This is a disaster.
More black holes!
What's happening here?
Oh my
god.
Okay, okay.
Let's head back up.
Let's remember down and to the right.
That's where we came from.
All right.
Down and to the right.
I remember this guy.
He's a nice landmark.
I have a feeling we cannot do anything here now.
Wait!
No, no, no!
Yeah, we can still...
Yes, man!
Oh!
Nice!
Oh, that's amazing.
Okay, never mind.
Everything's fine.
Everything is back on track.
Wait, weakening.
Hold on, that actually sounds pretty good.
Show me.
Target hit by a projectile that takes...
That's a sick modifier to have if you're using something explosive anyway.
That's dope.
I like it.
Get rid of the glowing land.
No longer friends with that.
Get rid of a hippie spread.
I hate that.
Get rid of this one because we don't have plasma anyway.
Uh, I want this.
Look
at that damage!
Look at that damage.
That's crazy.
I love this spell.
You can probably tell.
This is a great spell.
And you know what?
We can make it even greater.
Instead of speed up because we don't need that shit.
We're gonna go...
Wait, is that actually stacking?
Are we stacking this?
Uh...
Huh.
I'm not sure.
Man, it's the game slowing down every time I shoot this one.
No, actually, I don't think it is.
It just sounds like it.
But it's not.
Okay, water...
I mean, mana goes down quick.
Let me do this.
How much damage is this?
Wait, I can't even see the damage anymore.
I need to go to the other statue.
At some point, you break the statue so much, you can't even see what's happening anymore.
That statue is vibing.
Wait, what's...
Okay, no, no, no.
It's definitely better with that, I think.
Oh yeah, definitely.
But it feels like this is not doing anything.
Adding this extra one, am I crazy?
Whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Actually?
Holy fuck!
Yo, it's she...
Oh, that actually makes sense.
It shoots much longer.
I guess that makes sense.
If the spell has like a lifetime and you shoot it faster, it goes further before it dissipates.
But I'm just wondering why the reduced spread is not doing enough reducing of the spread.
Maybe because this is just in general like...
Is this actually useless then?
Oh, I think it is.
Reduced spread is useless on this one.
Aha!
That's good to know.
So what should we add in...
Maybe more mana.
Guys!
That's crazy!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Wow!
Do we even need a triple there?
Don't think so.
Holy shit!
That's wild!
Wait a minute, let me actually just try something.
Magic arrow?
How much does this do?
Not as much.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We gotta go with this one of course.
That is wild.
Let's see here.
It does 10 ice damage.
Speed of 220.
Okay.
I was about to see if it had any explosive effect, but it doesn't look like it.
But here's the thing.
I'm gonna go grab black holes now.
So I have them.
Oh, I just realized something by the way.
The thing that determines whether or not you can edit your wand in here is actually not whether or not you angered the gods.
It's whether or not it's collapsed.
That's the only thing that matters.
Because it's not collapsed, right?
I don't know why I thought it was the angering of the gods that determined that, but it's not.
Of course.
Can I... hold on.
Wait, down and right.
I already fucked up, I think.
But if I just keep...
damn.
If I just keep going right now, it should be okay.
This is toxic shit, so I'm not going that way.
Could be somewhere over here, I think.
Yeah, this is the spot.
That's one of them, I think.
There it is.
Thanks.
Now we keep exploring.
And now we do have a method to get back up if we want to.
Destroy that.
Very good.
And the interesting thing is I'm doing frost damage now.
So that also means I can freeze lava.
Even better.
You know?
Oh my god, come on.
I'm low on level...
Bunkle caves.
Is everything going to be...
Oh look, everything is lava.
It's actually disaster.
Good thing I found this, huh?
Just do a bit of that and then it's gone.
Heh heh.
What's that?
Lightning bolt, cool.
Personal gravity field.
Makes creatures hit by a projectile, gain a temporary gravity well that draws projectiles in.
Ah.
I am actually very curious about that.
How big that is.
Because let's say I hit an enemy with my freezing blast or freezing gaze.
Will all of those projectiles from the freezing gaze like bend towards the enemy then?
And do even more damage after the gravity field is active.
That's what I'm thinking.
Also really like lightning bolts.
Maybe I should drop these stones.
Maybe the rocks are like whatever now.
I feel like I've gotten so powerful the rocks are like whatever.
Maybe I'll keep one rock.
And then if I find a homing modifier later then I can think about using it again.
Yeah, I'm gonna do that.
I'm gonna take this and go back with it.
A bit tedious back and forth but it is what it is.
Oh no!
I can't touch that, that's bad.
Let's be careful here.
Toxic shit is bad.
What's this?
Oh, that's the other black hole one.
Actually, it's kind of quick when we have teleport.
Back we are.
Put this here.
Put some of them here.
This one can fuck off.
I like to try that.
In fact, maybe try that now.
Is the speed up actually necessary?
I think it is.
We definitely want more range.
Oh, is this gonna do anything in this current?
It is.
Okay, never mind.
Back it goes.
Double can go here.
Good.
Oh, actually hold on.
I'm scared.
Let's try.
Let's be somewhere safe.
Like here.
Let's go over here.
I just I need to see what this looks like.
I didn't dare hold down the button any longer.
Wait a minute.
Holy fuck.
Yo.
I mean.
It's a bit scary though.
You know?
Because, you know.
Actually, maybe in that case we don't even need this.
That's gonna make it even more scary.
Even though it is gonna kill me anyway.
Holy fuck.
That is crazy.
No, no, no, no.
That's I'm scared.
I'm too scared of that.
And we don't need it.
We don't need it, damn it.
Not yet though.
We need like electricity immunity and explosion immunity if I'm ever gonna do that.
For sure.
Yes.
And we do like that it's frost here.
Because if everything's lava, you know.
Good to have.
Yeah.
And then...
Wait a minute.
Did I never pick up the wand before I went back?
Oh wait, I did.
Never mind.
I did.
Let's go back again.
I got the stuff.
Personal gravity fields.
Gonna experiment with that later.
Aha!
Oh.
Didn't mean to freeze that, but shit.
It's toxic.
Oh no, how do I get that out?
Huh.
Dude, I can put out fire like this.
I didn't even consider that.
That is super effective against fire.
Oh, there we go.
Okay, I don't know what was in there.
But this is now molten metal.
And that is scary.
Look, fire gone.
Oh wait, wait, wait, wait.
Did I just turn that into molten metal now by doing that?
I'm too scared of trying to step on it.
I really want to experiment and see whether or not I actually do take damage from molten metal.
Logic would say, of course you do.
But who knows?
Maybe not.
You never know.
Bye-bye.
This one is actually so insane that when I shoot it in some direction, anything on that side of the screen just dies.
Doesn't matter where it is, it just dies.
Unless it's somehow immune to whatever damage I'm doing, right?
If it's like immune to frost damage.
That's the only exception, I think.
Wait, I don't know where I'm going.
I guess I'm going down.
We want to get to the next holy mountain and see the perks.
There's a guy there.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Don't touch molten metal.
It puts you on fire.
The problem is, the molten metal is so hard to see.
What is that?
Ice.
Oh, okay.
Like, I can't... is any of this bad for me?
What is this?
Frozen blood?
Damn.
Let me just have a quick peek.
Looks like a pirate.
And somehow he drops a million gold.
All right, go.
Next.
I feel like I don't have that much HP.
Spark bolt!
That... ooh.
Very nice.
I don't know what that is.
Holy shit.
What is all...
I forgot about you.
You still mad, huh?
Oh, he did.
Hold on.
Let's see here.
What do we got?
Fast movement?
Personal plasma beam?
Perk lottery?
Ooh.
Oh.
Oh, dude, invisibility.
I think I'm gonna perk lottery.
Sick!
That's awesome.
I won the lottery, boys.
Maybe I don't want these saw blade orbits.
They're kind of scaring me.
Scary.
Okay, give me...
That one.
What's in here?
Orbiting arc.
Dude.
Healing bolt?
Orbiting arc.
Oh.
What's happening?
Why was there a fire there just now?
Okay, ping pong path, linear arc.
Orange glimmer.
Protectile energy shield.
Gives a projectile a shield that deflects other projectiles.
Wait.
Wouldn't that mean if I just spam my button in any direction, any projectile shot against me will be deflected?
That seems crazy good.
If that's what I think, how that works, I can't speak English.
Uh, throw this wand away.
That seems crazy.
Oh, it looks sick!
I mean, less mana, of course.
Jesus.
Okay.
Let's see, what else do I want to try?
I don't know if I want this.
We'll have to see.
Because it means I have to give up something else like speed, you know, or...
I need to find a wand like this, but with more slots.
That would be the dream.
Maybe one of these is the dream.
No.
Uh, oh, this one, for sure.
Because look at this, damage.
Give me that.
And then we discard of the rest.
Heh heh.
I want this one as well, because it has both that...
And, hold on, I can throw this away.
You know what, spark bolt?
Let me actually just take a peek.
Yeah, that's quite nice.
We probably don't need that much mana then, because this costs no mana to shoot.
If we add this...
And then we add this one.
That's solid.
Honestly, that is really solid.
But I do like this.
You know, freezing gaze.
So good.
Maybe you don't need speed on this either.
It's already so fast.
So instead, we can maybe modify it even more.
Frozen charge, release an impact?
Yeah, I don't know, I don't know.
Wait.
Oh yeah, I have...
Oh my god.
The damage is crazy on this now.
Damn.
I feel like... wait.
Wait, I can take more perks?
Wait a minute!
Holy shit!
It's every time!
But, wow!
Really?
Hello?
That's insane!
I'm gonna recharge.
Because I don't like any of these.
Are you actually kidding?
That's insanity.
Wow.
Okay, I need to save money.
We're coming back here for sure.
I don't know, maybe I'll...
Call me crazy, but...
Something simple where...
Because the other one fills the entire screen.
That's the only thing I don't like about it.
It's too crazy.
You know?
This one is like...
You know what you're gonna get, sort of.
But then again...
The damage...
Is too good, isn't it?
To pass up?
I kind of forgot how I did this.
I had a speed, I had one of...
Did I have two of these?
No, because I felt like it didn't stack.
3,800...
Oh yeah, right, we had more mana.
Mana, mana, mana, mana, mana.
That's the thing.
Maybe we don't need to be able to spam it forever.
Because honestly, this is already good.
We don't need to be able to hold the button.
You know?
So maybe we'll try this.
Let's try it on these enemies.
Wait,
say what?
Oh, they're totally arcing!
Are they not?
They're arcing towards the target?
I'm not sure.
Oh my god, it's a sick wand.
We're not done.
What did I have here before?
What was happening?
Oh, there's a guy below me.
I don't remember what I...
I guess I just had an extra mana.
I mean, it is nice to hold it.
Actually, I was kind of feeling just now how annoying it was to have to pause.
So I think I like this more.
Now this one on here!
Hey!
Right?
Uh, this wand... hold on.
0.13.
I just want to see if I have a better wand just in general as well.
So I need to compare it to that, which is 0.13, 0.28.
Uh, no, unless...
Huh.
No, spells per cast, four.
I hate that.
Nope.
Okay, I'm gonna farm some money and re-roll.
That's crazy.
Oh, don't go up that way.
We don't want to collapse.
Look at this fool.
He actually...
He's actually kind of tangy.
Wait, he blocked!
What is he blocking?
I'm not quite sure what he's blocking there.
The red one... does that right.
Anger...
Yes,
I know.
I mean, they're already angry.
Who cares?
They're already angry.
Can they be even more angry?
I doubt it.
Actually, I maybe shouldn't say stuff like that.
Bye-bye.
Dude, if I go to the ancient laboratory now, I'm gonna slap everyone.
Oh god, cursed rock.
I must have hit one of those little crystals that do that.
Also, I already have enough money.
Let's go back.
Aha!
I can go like this now.
Watch.
Doink!
Okay.
What was I doing?
Oh yeah, re-roll.
I re-roll that shit.
I wonder if I get four more new ones or just two more new.
Aha!
Facing, projectile seemingly... that seems insane.
Bro, thanks.
Thanks for that.
That's exactly what I needed.
Thank you very much.
Danke schön.
I think it's time, boys.
We go up.
Oh wait, I never brought the black holes.
Fuck me.
Uh-oh.
Whoops.
Wait, do we have any method to...
Wait a minute.
Wait a second.
Can we really not get up?
Shit, we got...
Okay, you know, we gotta find something to dig with.
It's okay.
It happens.
You forget things sometimes.
That's okay.
But you know what?
Now that we have this, it's worth it.
You know?
Totally worth it.
That's what I tell myself.
Don't go in that projectile.
I need to find hearts.
Wow, this won't even dig through that.
That's insane.
All right, I can just...
It's a bit risky though when you don't know what's on the other side.
Wrong, wrong one.
I just used the absolutely wrong one there.
I didn't mean to teleport just now.
It's okay, we survived.
Sometimes I can't tell if they're dead or just frozen.
Uh, what?
My HP's won!
Uh...
I just got saved by a perk.
I don't know what the fuck just hit me in the face.
Someone hit me in the face with something just now.
And I don't know what it was.
I think it's over.
I think we're done here.
This is the end of the run.
I have no idea what just happened.
We need to find healing.
ASAP.
Oh man, it's actually over.
Like the smallest pixel of damage and I'm dead.
How am I gonna... hold on.
Let's see if we can't find a way up with what I currently have.
It's the only way to be safe.
We cannot go explore with 1h.
Actually, we're invisible.
No, but still.
That could be hazards.
Okay, so Sawblade Orbit actually sort of cuts through rock.
It makes it crumble.
That's an option.
If we play this safe with a long distance cast.
Hear me out.
We're gonna get rid of this.
Here, here, here, here.
Oh, we can't get hit by any falling rock.
Oh no, this is...
Holy shit.
Let me think, let me think.
Is there a worm that has made a path somewhere?
Oh, damn
it.
I need to think.
I think I'm gonna try the Sawblade.
Oh man, but the thing is, I'm so scared of launching it in a wrong manner and just dying.
Because that is a scary weapon.
Let's say I put...
What is a good one?
What is a good example here?
What could we use?
Something simple.
Like an energy orb.
That's simple, isn't it?
It's simple.
So we put long distance cast on that.
And then we add a sawblade orbit on top of that.
Like that.
Please don't kill me.
Okay, wait, it has three spells, so...
One.
This is just modifier.
It should be fine.
Okay, okay.
Not bad.
Hey, that's not bad.
That's not bad.
Okay, good, good, good.
Emergency...
Let's get...
Wait a minute.
What am I trying to do here?
I'm trying to...
Put things in...
No, I'm gonna keep that wand.
I need mana.
I need this to go faster, basically.
So what I need is...
Hold on.
What is the issue here?
Recharge.
Recharge time.
That's the issue.
Let's do this one then.
Here, here, here.
Wait, is it actually digging properly?
It is, it is, it's working.
It's working.
It's definitely working.
Is this collapsed?
No, okay.
So I just need to do that, basically.
So, okay, let me think.
How do I actually heal now?
Do I have any healing anywhere?
Oh, let me think, let me think.
Healing...
Do I even...
I need to go to the next holy mountain.
That's the only way.
Okay, new plan.
We're gonna invisibility our way to the portal and go to the next holy mountain.
We actually don't have any healing.
I'm gonna use this here.
Because we can...
Oh wait, we can change wands everywhere.
Yeah, we can change wands everywhere.
This is fine.
Let's soft blade orbit on...
Yeah, this one is...
Don't accidentally use this wand right now.
In fact, don't even have it equipped.
Just do something like that instead.
And then swap it out when we need.
We're gonna stay invisible now.
This is the mission, okay?
Am I stained?
Okay, there we go, there we go.
Okay.
Splinter cell time.
Quietly...
As quiet as a church mouse.
Ah!
I got a heart attack!
No!
Fuck me.
Okay.
Take two.
Quiet as a church mouse and we watch out for traps.
Watch for traps, watch for traps.
Don't teleport to the other side of a wall if you don't know what's there.
I see a trap there.
Let's go on top first.
Because we can't get...
What the hell is that even?
I don't know what that is and it scares me.
If I use teleport, I...
Why am I revealed?
Okay, I guess I can't teleport without being revealed.
That's fine.
Why am I hearing flapping?
Someone's flapping.
This is flapping.
The plastic is flapping.
I can't touch this cursed rock.
Or I will die.
This is a death trap.
This whole place is...
Look for traps.
Hopefully there are no enemies that can just randomly see me.
Because that's their ability or something.
Go.
Go!
Okay, okay.
I've already accepted my death, by the way.
I've accepted this run is over.
So whatever happens now, it's fine.
I am ready.
I'm pretty much dead.
That's what I'm seeing here.
I don't know what this...
I don't know if this AOE will damage me.
I don't think it does, but I just don't want to take the risk.
Go.
Uh-oh.
I can't face through enemies, right?
Oh my god.
Look for traps.
Clear.
Uh...
That was a...
That was an arrow.
That just...
There's a trap up there.
I don't want to shoot though.
I don't want to reveal.
Oh!
The traps can somehow see me.
That's so bullshit.
This shield has saved my ass.
Holy crap.
My hands are sweaty.
Mom is preparing the spaghetti.
Oh no, I can't get further down here.
Oh, that's...
I don't like any of these surfaces.
Okay, I could teleport down here on the other side, but I could die immediately if I do it.
I don't know what's on the other side.
We don't take that chance.
Nope, nope, nope.
Holy god.
I have to.
I can't go anywhere.
I mean, there's a path I haven't tried.
But it's risky.
Go.
Touch anything here and I'm dead.
Let's be careful of the traps on the way up.
Wait, there's a chest in there.
Oh, don't even be tempted.
We're not going for that.
Holy shit.
Any traps?
Okay, okay.
Dude,
my hands are so sweaty.
They're fighting each other.
That's okay.
As long as they don't get anything on me, like some kind of stain on me.
Blood stain or something.
That I'm done for.
I don't even want to risk picking up that wand in case it reveals me.
Any traps on the walls?
I'm not seeing any.
No traps here.
Oh, okay.
Oh, my lord.
Oh no, I can't get further down.
Any traps?
I don't see any.
Uh-oh, this is a dangerous spot.
If I touch the enemies, I die, right?
Oh, huh?
I think it was aiming for that guy over there and I died.
Maybe I was revealed for a second.
I don't know.
That's it.
That was such a good run, though.
I have no fucking idea.
How I just went from full HP to zero or like one, I guess.
But I was basically dead there if it wasn't for the perk.
Like, what the fuck?
The fuck was that?
Just a random ass mage.
Like, insta killed me.
I have no idea how that even happens.
That's insane.
All right.
Well, we go again.
I also, honestly, I may have been, like, really lucky with a bunch of drops and all that, but I didn't get any hearts that run.
Like, I had no HP.
300 HP is like nothing at that point in the game.
I feel like you just lose that in a matter of seconds, you know?
I feel like I could have found way more hearts.
It was just so unlucky with that.
Or maybe I explored in a bad way.
I didn't find any.
Definitely needed more HP.
Let's scour this first level.
And you know what?
I will try my utmost to not pick up the healing in the holy mountains from now on.
Because they are so valuable.
Like, every single point of healing you can get in this game is so incredibly valuable.
Like I said this before, but if, let's say you, what's this?
Swamp potion.
Yeah, I don't like swamp.
Let me get water.
Um, like if you take like 80 damage in the first level, right?
And you pick up the healing.
So you heal 80 damage.
That's a wasted potential 3000 heal.
If you later on get that much HP, you know?
So the more damage you take in the early levels here, the more it's gonna fuck you later.
It's like a compounding thing.
I was just about to teleport through this wall.
But I can't do that.
Okay, now that we have water, we can be a little more brazen.
But that was, that was a great run, man.
I had great perks and a great wand as well.
Everything was just aligning, you know?
It was great.
Purifying powder.
That's right.
I found this once.
Can I drink it?
I am now purified.
My body is free of toxins.
I have been cleansed.
Imagine if that's how easy it is.
Electrolytes.
I keep wanting to teleport through the wall.
Let me do this.
That's the most satisfying sound effect when that thing activates.
Oh, come on.
Really?
Don't even think I can fit there.
Maybe.
No.
Okay.
Go another way.
I was a bit too close there.
Yeah.
Oh, there's a chest.
What was in there?
A bomb?
Was there a bomb in the chest?
I'm glad I didn't do that.
Go close to that, huh?
I thought it was one of those Kiba Skibi thingies.
But that wasn't it.
That was a bomb inside that chest, man.
How evil.
Man, this is scuffed.
I can't go anywhere on the right side.
Let me go left.
We're going this way now.
So quiet.
Hello.
Sweet.
That was smooth.
Almost got hit by that horta.
Basically, my goal here is to not take any damage in the first level because then that means I have another free healing for later.
Assuming I can get back up, of course.
But at that point, and like when you're that deep in the game, you should have something, right?
At least chances are you're going to have something.
Man, I haven't seen a single hemisphere.
This is the hemisphere.
Come on, guys.
Where the fuck are you?
Oh, we require water.
Hey, man.
It's probably not dead yet.
Get him.
That is oil.
Is this guy still throwing fireballs?
He went all the way down there.
I kind of want to take care of him first so he don't fuck me later.
Oh, no, not that guy.
Oh, no.
That's bad.
Bad news.
In fact, hold on.
Hey, that worked so well.
It's basically like a little mine.
Dude, I have a new appreciation for this spell.
Like, you put it there, you wait.
Oh, okay, that didn't trip.
That's neat.
Wait, how much damage does that do?
130.
That is sick.
And we have a one, two.
What the fuck?
That's just a spell refresher here.
I have never seen that.
Huh?
Isn't that weird?
What the hell?
Burn my way through that wood.
Hemis!
Uh-oh.
Let me try the...
Uh...
Hey, sir.
Yeah.
It works.
Oh my god, it's so good!
Oh, yeah, right.
Don't go near yourself.
That's a good lesson.
That's lava.
Whoa!
I think there's still pixels of lava here.
I gotta be careful.
Yeah.
Okay, we're fine now.
This is not a very organized method of exploration that I'm doing here.
It's okay, though.
That connects back up there.
I could set fire at that.
But I only have three crystals left.
What's that?
Oh, volcanic sand.
Slimy egg.
Oh.
Yeah, no.
Oh wait, I can't kill it.
Okay, that's fine.
I just hate that it's gonna shoot projectiles that release a...
poison and shit that's gonna affect me.
Even though its intentions are good, you know?
It's still gonna mess me.
Oh, hello there.
It's Barney.
Aha, there's the portal.
Well, one of them.
In fact, there's another one right here, too.
They're always right next to each other.
I wonder if that's consistent.
Another one?
Or is that the same?
Maybe the same.
Sure.
I mean, this is good to know for later if we find healing.
You know?
Like, now, see, now there's poison here.
Go away.
I don't want you.
Hemis.
This is the Hemis hub.
Oh, he's gonna kill them.
Come on, slime man.
Do your thing.
Oh no, it's dripping fire.
You can totally put out fire with your shots.
Sort of.
What's that?
Gunpowder post?
I don't think gunpowder would be something you would put in a powder container, given that it's a powder.
Right?
Weird.
I could water him.
Or I could crystal him.
Maybe he walks in that water and that would be great.
I'm gonna make a little pool here for when he comes down.
This is genius.
Somewhat genius.
Yeah!
Oh, I'm out of water.
This is a disaster.
Okay, nice.
That was scary.
There's a Hemis here.
Thank you.
I can't believe I just found a spell refresher just sitting there in the middle of the map.
For some reason, my brain can't compute.
Oh god.
Fuck off, will ya?
Man, it went perfect and now you showed up!
Fuck you, I'm out of here.
I'm at 100 HP, damn it!
Fuck!
I hate you.
I will not take that out of spite.
I'm not healing.
Nope.
We're not healing.
Let's see what perks we get.
Hey, what's this?
Breathless.
You can no longer drown and can move in liquids with ease.
Pretty cool, I guess.
Hi, man and loca.
Nah, I don't want that.
Vampirism!
We're back, boys!
We're back.
We will drink the remains of our enemies and get back to former glory.
Hell yeah.
I'm still not healing.
I'm not taking that heal over there.
I'm saving it.
Okay, let's see here.
Shuffle.
Oh, you know what?
This is not bad.
This costs...
seven...
Oh, I think I want this for sure.
And that one.
Let me see.
It has 190 mana.
52.
This costs 80.
I kind of just want this.
Am I crazy?
In fact, put them in the water.
Sweet!
Yeah, I like it.
Yeah, I like that.
We can even get a rock in case we get infinite spells.
That's a nice one.
Hit that one.
Even though we already had two.
Yeah, I actually didn't think about that.
Bombs could be nice to have.
More of them at least.
What is this one again?
Oh, the fireball.
Give me that one.
And put it here.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Let's rock.
We have a decent damage wand now.
Like this right here is actually sick.
It does 25 damage.
Is there any way for us...
We can't get out of here, unfortunately, without collapsing.
But it is what it is.
Wait, that's the wrong one.
Yeah!
Wow, a lot of lava came out of that little fly.
Also, I need more water.
I don't got any.
I refuse to heal.
Oh, I still haven't died today.
The first one doesn't count.
Oh, shit.
That was the second, wasn't it?
Dammit.
I thought I still had one.
So, wow, these guys release more lava than usual.
Or maybe I'm imagining it.
Hold on, can this...
Wait a minute, let me try something.
It actually does.
I remember this now.
I tried this once before, remember?
It can shoot through the walls.
Okay, well, you know, there may or may not be a lesson here.
And Karma, regarding the whole, I refuse to take the healing.
But let's just gloss over that part.
That's not important.
It doesn't matter.
That was actually really funny.
All right, we go again.
Also, hold on.
I need to think...
One, two...
I don't remember how many times I died now.
Wait, how do I see this?
I need to update the title.
Okay, guys, how many times did I die?
Did you see?
I'm gonna look at Shadd in a second.
I was at 61.
And was that after the first death or the second?
I think we're at 62.
Right?
I'm gonna say 62.
I mean, worst case is probably 63.
Can't be more than 63.
Oh, 63 now?
Okay, thanks.
I just needed to ask.
Okay.
Let's move.
Got bouncing burst, which is honestly the worst fucking spell in the game for me.
At least of the starter ones you get.
I hate it so much.
Back in the hemisphere.
If you get here too much, it starts to become the himishame.
The Shamesphere.
That's perfect.
Oh, god.
And we have water.
Lovely.
That's a good start.
Chemists.
I require at least five hearts from this region.
I take no less, no more.
Oh, maybe I take more, but no less.
Here.
You like that?
Hey, fucker.
Water for you.
Just gotta die from that.
Oh, I got him.
Nice.
The water strikes again.
So good.
Give me this one as well.
Chemists.
What's up there?
Oh, that's a lot of oil.
That is a lot.
Makes me think that may be a puzzle of some sort.
Don't touch that rock.
I wonder if you're immune from explosions when you're diving on the water.
Even though explosions on the water is actually more dangerous than above water.
But still, I wonder.
Oh my god.
Everyone's shooting green shit, including me.
Ah, not this dude.
Ah, what do I have?
I actually have these.
I have some sick abilities.
Oh my god.
He released a copious amount of that.
Look at this scream.
That's not normal, is it?
Why did he release so much?
Holy shit.
Okay, well, whatever.
Doesn't hurt me.
A magic arrow.
That's better.
Dude, imagine getting the lottery in the first mountain.
That would be crazy.
Whoops!
Fuck.
I was in the...
I can teleport through this mindset with a teleport wand still.
I can't believe I was still in that mindset.
I like just instinctively switch to my two and try to go through the wall.
Fuck.
That is a rough mistake.
Oh, nice.
I get rewarded at least.
I will take this.
Very good.
I am happy again.
But I'm not.
My happiness is yet to be completely full.
I need a bit more.
Is that
gold?
Chaotic polymorphine?
What's going on up here?
Multiple platforms, eh?
That's curious.
Oh my god.
Maybe it's not that curious.
I had no patience for him.
Diminution potion!
What does that mean?
Drink.
Weakness.
You feel weakened.
Cost-ingestin...
Diminution?
Oh, like diminishing effect.
Interesting.
Diminution.
So I guess I pour this on enemies and they do less damage or something.
That's pretty cool.
I've never seen that.
I can't believe the game is still throwing shit at me.
I haven't seen yet.
You know?
Like last time when I saw all those bottles lined up.
Looked almost like an apothecary.
Wait, how am I gonna...
There we go.
Wait, did I ever go on top of the mountain and grab the health?
I don't think I did.
I just auto-piloted in here.
And now I don't have enough to get it.
Unless I find another wand.
I
think I was just in disbelief over my own...
Over the karma that I suffered.
You know, in that death.
I can't get through there.
I don't want to spend another explosion on it.
Oh my god.
Is that Barney?
Gimme.
Like, I can't get to those guys.
Porta?
Hemis?
Anything with an H.
Whoops, didn't mean to shoot it.
Damn it.
Let's just break it entirely.
Just get it over with.
I'm going around.
Thank you.
And I still haven't killed the boss over there, which is presumably the first boss ever.
I can't believe how hard he is.
I really need to get on that.
He seems pretty hardcore.
Nice.
Oh, the gold appeared up here.
So weird.
There's the portal.
Wait a minute.
We have a worm.
There's a worm on the loose.
Oh no.
Hopefully it's not going to anger any gods, because I'm not prepared for that.
Please no.
Don't make them angry.
Please.
Oh, this...
What the...
Oh!
He was right there.
Okay.
Crap.
Well, that's an issue.
That is real bad.
I'm not ready to go through yet.
To find at least one more wand.
It's very important.
Wait a minute, why is there...
What's going on here?
Polymorphine?
Nobody likes that.
Oh?
Ah, collapsed mines.
Oh god, oh god, oh god.
Okay.
Ah, shit!
Goddammit!
This is an issue.
Hopefully my...
Magic missile will be enough.
I'm going to grab the spell refresher and try and fuck him up.
That's going to be my way to do it.
I don't know how else I'm going to do it.
He's going to really mess with me.
I want to get in there.
Do I actually... hold on.
Do I want to get in there?
Is there anything in the oil?
There is not.
Never mind.
What's that?
Flammoxium.
Ooh, that's bad.
I don't want anything like that in my life.
I'm actually scared of walking through these tunnels because if the worm suddenly appears there, I'm dead.
Do not go through those tunnels.
Not yet, at least.
Holy shit, this worm has been at work!
Damn!
All right, I think it's time.
Let's just go.
500 gold?
Not bad.
I'm not going to heal.
58 is okay.
Oh wait, he's here.
Oh no.
Maybe there's something in one of these ones?
Teleport is definitely nice.
Oh god.
Oh no.
Tell me, tell me this is going to damage him.
It reflects off!
I'm dead!
It's over.
Run!
Nah, man.
What can I do?
I don't...
Jesus Christ, man.
I felt like I was just incredibly unlucky there.
Wow.
Well, okay.
The game was like, no, you don't get to do anything this time.
And I'm just sitting here like, okay.
Well, that's okay.
Because now I'm going to go up here and grab that health.
That's surely going to change everything.
Just you watch.
Grab this.
I think two dynamites is enough if you do it correctly.
I just didn't do it correctly.
Thanks.
Solid.
That's 25 in the bank.
And if we somehow manage to find a decent one, we could go do the worm thing.
You know, be able to see and then head into the dark cave.
And then we can get at least two more.
25 HPs.
So that's 50 HP right there.
That would be pretty sweet.
It's actually solid.
What's that?
What is it with all this flammoxium?
Flammoxium everywhere right now.
Hmm.
Maybe I want it.
Just take it.
It's safer in my possession than it is just sitting there, you know.
Hey, the gods are smiling upon me today.
Very cool.
Thank you.
Hey, miss.
That's surely a good sign too.
We have the whiskey.
Oh.
Come here.
He's drunk now.
You fucker.
Mother fucker.
I was playing it so carefully with you and you somehow still manage to get the shot on me.
Absolute asshole.
Now you can stay in there.
I don't care about you.
That's fine.
What's this?
Pheromone?
What's going on there?
Is that pheromone?
It is.
What happened here?
Why is the rock wall loose like that?
Say what now?
I kind of want to dig there.
Yeah, okay, so we're here now.
I...
So there are some things like this, for example, is always the same.
You know, it always goes down to some height and then it goes right and then you have this part.
So right now my map is ultra correct when it comes to this place.
As a wand!
Let's see.
A bomb.
Always welcome.
Here, that's one for you.
Hopefully that killed someone.
It sure did.
Toxic sludge potion.
Berserk you.
You piece of shit.
Just jumps out of nowhere and shoots my ass off there.
That's annoying.
That's the second one.
In fact, I'm going to go swimming in here.
Yay!
Huh, yep, that's a lot of berserkium.
Kind of want to grab some for myself.
And there's a treasure chest too.
Kind of want to get that without disturbing the berserkium.
Let's see how we can do this.
We have TNT.
If I do it correctly, I can blow up here and get it.
I'm going to do that.
I like having all this berserkium at my fingertips.
Oh, how do I...
I may have to use another TNT to get through here first.
Now I have to do this precisely timed.
Watch this.
Oh, beautiful!
And a water potion.
Not bad.
I needed that anyway to fill up my berserkium.
Let's put the water down here.
Just empty that bad boy.
Go, go, go.
I may even put that here.
The phlamoxium, I kind of want to get rid of as well.
And then fill that with the berserkium too.
Wouldn't that be cool?
I'm going to phlamox the shit out of this place right here.
Actually, I think it's more correct to say I'm going to phlamox the shit out of it.
Not phlamox.
There we go.
We're going to be critting so much.
No, we're going to be doing double damage, right?
That's what that does.
Double dude, berserkium.
Really ought to utilize that more and that's what I'm doing now.
Okay, sweet.
This is going pretty well so far.
69 HP, nice.
I could open up over there.
Let's do it.
There's a big stack of explosions.
That's acceleration.
Isn't that going to break under that fire?
Maybe not.
You died so quick because of my berserkium.
Should I go swimming in this?
Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't even get through.
Bad, bad, bad.
Don't want to be near the fire with all this oil.
Where am I not explored?
Here.
Bunch of pheromone up there with...
I think phlamoxium too.
Nice.
Oh, I didn't even see that.
Frightened me.
Okay, this bastard.
He's not going to get the best of me this time.
This time I'm ready.
Come on.
I'm taking no chances here.
Shit, I didn't even hit him.
Hold on, I'm going to flank him.
If I can.
Oops.
Oh, wait a minute, him is...
Yes, this is it.
This is the flank.
Except he's already seeing in my direction.
Oh no.
Bastard.
Got him!
Feels amazing, man.
After what he's done to me today, in the last 10 minutes...
That felt good.
Oh, there's a chest there.
Imagine if that's another heart.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh my god!
Love it!
Oh, look at this.
Oh, that guy is in berserkium?
That is scary.
Maybe I'll just dispatch him with a good old bomb, huh?
Or TNT.
And he's gone.
Pheromone, berserkium and lava.
What a combo.
What do we got?
Freezing liquid.
Gunpowder...
Ambrosia, that's nice.
I think I want that.
In fact, I want two Ambrosia.
Damn it.
That's okay.
I got him.
I got him!
As far as I know, you actually take no damage.
When you have that...
Another heart!
This is a great start.
Wow.
I can't be jinxing anymore.
This guy is flummoxed to the max.
Maximus flamoxius.
300 gold?
That's not a lot.
We could get some more.
Clear.
Thank you very much.
Oh, what's this?
Oh, it's just the entrance.
Look different to me for some reason.
Oh yeah, that's a dead end.
Imagine if you find more hearts in here.
Like, isn't even possible.
You know?
It's already been so good.
There's no way there can be more.
Imagine if a heart was hiding underneath this pile of coal.
You know what?
I'm almost religious at this point.
I'm gonna try.
Burn.
Watch.
Okay, never mind.
I don't want to wait for that.
Fuck it!
I thought it would be like something I could reveal instantly.
Wait.
Wait, didn't I see this exact thing just before?
Like, the minecart with the thing on top and two explosives?
I destroyed that.
That's such a weird coincidence.
What are the chances of that, I wonder?
Yeah, he's gonna die.
I see you.
Yeah, shoot him for me.
Good.
In fact, yeah, just bomb him.
There we go.
I have no patience for those shotgunners.
Not after what they've done to me.
The scars run deep.
I can't get through there.
That is a lot of oil.
Am I in a collapsed mine yet?
I don't think so.
Oh, there we go.
I'm gonna...
Oh, this guy almost got me again.
Bastard.
In fact, I have energy spheres.
Why don't I use those?
Don't hit me.
Scary.
See ya, Horta.
See ya in hell.
A chest!
Uh, an Ukuskivi.
Oh, wait a minute.
Hey, that makes sense.
Watch this.
Uko.
Wait, I've never been killed by one of them?
That's almost unbelievable.
Huh.
So this...
So I guess...
Maybe scivi means stone.
Uku means electricity.
Electric stone.
And maybe that guy is just called electric.
Or he's the cable man, of course.
I can't get up there.
I don't want to grab that.
I'm scared of electricity.
Acid potion?
Hell no.
Okay, that's good.
I have immense fear of fighting these enemies in narrow corridors here, where I can't jump up or down very much.
That's the worst.
Uh, I feel like something is up there.
Hmm.
I'm gonna bet on it.
Watch this.
There's gonna be something insane up here.
And when I say that, I mean insanely useless.
That's what I meant.
Hopefully that's not gonna explode.
In fact, I don't trust it.
Hey, another heart!
Wow.
We are blessed.
Insano style.
All right, this thing's gonna explode for sure.
Don't trust it.
I'm playing so save right now and I'm proud of myself.
Got it.
Always have your water thing full.
Uh-oh.
Look at the HP on that guy.
Portal down there.
Can't believe I only have 400 gold.
I feel like I've killed a shit ton of enemies.
But I also played save, so I didn't pick up the gold all the time.
Wait.
What?
Hold on.
Fuck me.
Didn't even make it through.
I didn't mean to do that.
Can I just get through here, please?
I have no more.
That's it.
I have one bomb left now.
Fuck's sake.
Well, that's useless.
That was the biggest fail ever.
All I wanted was to get through the floor.
Dang it.
Wait, I can't even...
All right, I'm gonna use my bomb.
I don't care.
I have a feeling.
Oh, wait a minute.
I'm actually...
Hold on a second.
I'm draining.
I mean, if I can't see, it doesn't matter.
If there's no water.
Right?
Let's wait.
This is gonna be a mess.
But all this water is the water we traversed when we went through the caves.
It's almost completely empty.
This is actually a legit strategy.
I think.
Oh, but I still can't see anything.
Oh, I'm actually tempted to go for the worm.
Am I crazy?
Ah, I don't know, man.
I'm tempted.
Hmm.
It's still draining.
Actually, hold on.
It's sort of...
It drains out over here as well.
And then down there.
Given enough time.
Hmm.
Let me move on.
I think the strategy is sound.
But I'm still scared.
Because what if there's an enemy in there and I can't see?
You know, sometimes these enemies fucking pop out of nowhere.
And that scares me.
So, and I'm at 69 HP.
I don't want to take that risk, actually.
I changed my mind.
Frogs on the left.
Shotgun man.
Don't you think about it?
Yeah, go to the frogs.
I wonder if they will hurt him.
Or if he will hurt the frogs.
All right, let me prepare a little bath for you.
I'm gonna run a bath for you.
There you go.
Take a bath.
Jump in that.
Yeah, come on.
Go to the left.
Nice warm bath.
That's it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Back to the bath.
Yes, in there.
Stay there.
That's good.
That's my boy.
No, no, no.
Come on, stay in.
You're like a fucking cat.
Come on.
In you go.
You know you want to get me.
I'm over here.
Oh yeah, Berserkium.
Drink that.
Sweet.
Go in the water.
Shit, he's actually after me.
This is a crazy duel.
This fucker hit me.
He's gonna kill me.
This is personal.
I need to kill him.
Yeah, you like that?
You mad?
You mad, bruh?
Yes.
Come on.
And for the final...
Watch this.
Shit.
No!
Okay, he died, he died.
Ha, bitch!
See ya.
I'm out of here.
Hashtag worth it.
Okay.
Uh, we should heal.
What do we got?
Uh, we have...
Let's see the perks.
Trick greed.
4x instead of 2x gold is dropped when death is an accident.
Okay, I'm still not quite sure what that means.
Now this one is not bad.
It's actually not bad.
But it also feels like...
I would rather have something else.
You know what I mean?
It feels like a consolation perk.
In a way.
What the hell?
Something just exploded.
Luminous drill.
Actually, there's some decent spells here.
I like it.
I like this.
I like this one.
Wait, what's this?
Electric torch.
No, thanks.
Give me the double.
Give me that one.
Give me...
Spark bold with explosion?
If that works...
So I think this works exactly like when this hits something, it explodes, basically.
Hey!
How much damage?
68?!
Dude, that's insane.
How is that not like, really good?
Oh, okay, I need mana enough for it to actually explode.
So I need to put this...
Oh no, okay.
But that's really good.
That's not bad at all.
Maybe I'll take this one.
Yeah, I'll give you this one as well.
Fire bolt with trigger.
Maybe just another spark bolt for later.
It's only 15.
Give me that one too.
I think I like this.
This is good.
This is solid.
This is actually solid damage, you know?
It's like a shotgun, basically, right now.
I'm not gonna use spell refresh here.
You may think I'm crazy, but...
No, I don't want it.
I will use this.
I can dig a little bit.
And of course...
That's great, that's...
Ooh.
Yo, that's pretty much a lightsaber, look!
They've only had some add mana on that.
Pretty neat.
I like that a lot.
Okay.
I will re-roll the perk.
God damn it.
I don't want these.
I'm moving on.
I'm gonna maybe pick that one later.
That one is for ultra-late game.
Wait, hold on.
Yeah, it's the one-off thing.
All right!
Let's go.
This is sweet.
Like, look at that!
That spark bolt has some spark.
You sense lucrative opportunities?
Do I?
Do I actually?
What do you mean by that?
Maybe it means enemies drop more gold.
Let me try and pay attention.
Drops one.
Maybe they're worth more?
That's a lot of lava.
Okay.
Wait, can I dig with this?
Ah, not really.
At least not on stone.
Maybe coal.
We'll have to see.
Otherwise, I have this actually.
Oh yeah.
Oh wait, is that what it means?
There's a bunch of gold in the rock.
Look, there's way more than usual.
You see that?
That has to be what that means.
Oh man, I need...
Okay, I need something to dig with.
And then I'm going nuts.
Oh my god, it's...
It's just lying there.
Okay, I'm definitely feeling lucrative opportunities now.
I understand what you mean, game.
Oh yeah.
That means I can get back and re-roll.
Holy shit, it's everywhere.
Are you gonna shotgun me?
Fuck you.
Got him.
Can I dig here?
It's decent.
Oh, that bounces off.
That's useless.
Like, oh no.
Wait, I don't have water.
Oh no.
I forgot to bring water.
The classic mistake.
That just cost me so much.
God damn it.
I'm gonna back up.
Gotta grab that water.
Wait, can I...
Can I even get back up?
I think so.
Wait a sec.
No, that gives no recoil.
Maybe this one?
Shit!
Wait, how do I get back up?
Oh wait, never mind.
There's water here.
I see water.
I will get rid of berserkium.
Because ambrosia is more rare.
In fact, I see that so rarely.
I should hold on to it.
In fact, I should just drink it.
What am I doing?
Fucking hell, I'm dumb.
I'll put this here and go.
There we go.
Okay, better.
Now we're safe against fire, sort of.
More than before.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god, there's so much gold.
Imagine if I had a proper digging wand.
Damn.
I would be rich.
Beyond my wildest dreams.
Like look at this, it's just lying there in the open.
You just sort of walk on it.
This is awesome.
Aha!
A digging wand?
Sort of.
Essence to power?
And bombs?
Sure.
Why not?
I'm already rich, it's wild.
Whoops, didn't mean to hit that one.
I gone and did it.
Why is my screen shaking so much?
Spitter bolt.
Let me try something.
Oh yeah.
Dude, the water is actually sick.
Look at that.
Fire gone.
Yeah.
Does spitter bolt dig?
It doesn't.
That's fine, I like this.
I like this a lot.
I'm gonna be here a while, man.
I'm gonna be looting all of this.
It's gonna be so neat.
I'm gonna go back up.
I'm gonna re-roll the perks.
Oof.
Oh yeah, baby.
That's mysterious.
Man, this explosion one is insane.
Like imagine I had a wand where this doesn't run out of mana and I can do this with every shot.
How is that not insane?
And a wand in there.
I was just about to try and teleport through the wall again.
It's free digging!
Come here.
I sense lucrative opportunities.
Very lucrative.
Yeah, you know what?
Okay, instead of wasting so much time trying to dig with this, I'm gonna walk around the entire level.
If I find something better to dig with, I use that and comb the area.
That's the new plan.
Unless it's like really right there in my face.
Then I'll take it, you know?
What's over here?
Can't get through.
Gold.
Bye-bye.
I did 170 damage just there.
That's gonna burn.
Hey, sweet.
Look.
That was easy.
Bunch of gold.
A wand.
Let's see it.
Light.
Ah, no.
No, thanks.
I'm good.
Oh my god, I'm gonna be so rich.
I can do re-rolls forever.
Oh my god, stop.
Almost 2k.
Oh my god.
Careful here.
Oh, shit.
I really hate these guys.
I feel like I'm having more trouble with them now.
Than I did early on.
Like they were never really a big problem.
But now they suddenly are.
Look at that shit.
Still manages to hit me.
You better die from this.
That was a fireworks show.
Hey, there we go.
Look at this.
Now we're talking.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, we're gonna be so rich.
Ah.
That guy picked up my wand.
Yeah, it's not very good, brother.
I'm sorry.
Wait, I kind of forgot I had...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, I've been super dumb.
I forgot I had this wand.
How good is this?
Oh my god.
I've been able to do this the entire time.
What is wrong with me?
Are you kidding me?
What is happening?
That's unreal.
Look at that.
Holy shit.
I mean, it's not as good, I don't think.
I think I prefer the other one.
But just the fact that I didn't even remember that.
That's just unreal.
Thanks.
Holy shit.
This is actually insane digging.
Look at that.
It goes through rock too.
No problem.
Oh, be careful not to get hit by those.
There we go.
Man is good on it too.
Like it lasts a while, you know?
Okay, I hate that these are like floating like...
I need to be close to the wall when I do it.
So that they always explode.
Oh shit, I hit myself just there, see that?
Oh my god, this is dangerous.
Maybe I don't like this wand now.
Change my mind.
I just need to be like a little distance away and then it's okay.
Like not right next to it, but like, you know, almost.
Wait, are they seeking?
The hell?
Why is that not taking damage?
That's weird.
There we go.
Oh yeah, they automatically home.
That makes more sense now.
I didn't remember that.
Oh shit.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
That guy's dead, what is that?
Teleportation.
Let's be careful around that.
Neat.
What the hell is that blue?
Blue fungus!
Say what?
I am so rich.
It's actually disgusting.
I should totally go back and...
But can I go back though?
I don't, I can't get up.
I need a teleport wand or something.
What's happening here?
Oh, let's blow it up.
Cool.
There's a large amount of gunpowder.
Fungal caverns!
Should we get high?
Air feels extremely humid.
Let's get high.
Yeah, oh yeah.
Oh shit!
Yeah, we gotta get out of here.
Excuse me.
Eat the mushroom.
Eat it.
Oh, I'm high as fuck right now.
Usual concepts don't apply.
Is this enough?
It is.
Word copper.
Again.
Okay, so copper has changed.
I'm actually so curious to see what it's changed to.
Oh, will you stop burning?
Oh, I am tripping right now, man.
A what?
What's happening there?
Look at that!
I've never seen that.
Okay, how do I get in there?
It's all metal.
Hold on.
Say what?
Can I have from the top maybe?
The hell is this?
Slimy egg?
That wand better be insane.
Ah, damn it, I can't get through with that.
Alright, we gotta come back here with something that can get through there.
We gotta check that out.
Let me go back in here.
That is a dead end.
Hey, I missed.
There we go.
Ow, I hurt myself again.
At this point, I'm the one doing the most damage to myself.
Not the enemies.
It's me.
What the...
Just stay at a safe distance while I use this.
Llamoxium.
No, thanks.
Whoa.
Those guys.
Bye-bye.
Nice, a wand?
Ghostbuster?
Uh-oh, there's a bunch of enemies down there.
Oh, no!
Holy shit!
Leave!
What is happening?
Bro, it's over.
We're done.
We're done here.
100%.
We're done.
There's no way.
Yep.
Holy fucking shit!
That went from zero to 100 so quick!
Wow!
Holy crap!
I got my ass kicked.
Wow.
Alright.
Well, that's it for now, man.
It's almost been six hours.
Actually, it's six hours and 30 minutes.
I played a lot.
Whew!
That was a tough session, dude.
Let me change that.
65 deaths.
Holy crap.
How are you guys doing?
There's no way you could be suffering more than me.
Neuter giveth?
Neuter taketh away.
That's the best thing I've read.
That's so true.
Have fun.
Six hours and 30 minutes.
Yeah, it was fun, man.
Oh, man.
That one death with the mage that somehow killed me in one hit.
I can't get over that.
That felt bad, man.
But it was a good run.
Is your CPU maybe old?
Which explains why the game was lagging that one time.
It is possible.
I definitely have an older CPU.
I have a risen 3700X.
But for a game like this, it should be okay for that, I think.
But then again, there's a lot to simulate in this game.
Oh, yeah, I can go back and watch the VOD for sure.
I'm actually going to do that.
In fact, there's something else I want to check anyway to update my map.
So I'll be checking the VOD to update the map as well.
Noita only uses like five cores, so that's kind of explains the lag.
That's an impressive amount, though.
Most games don't use more than one.
At least, as far as I know, it's very hard to paralyze games like this.
Oliver, instead of restarting the game, you can go to mods and press restart with mods for quicker restart.
But is that just going to launch it normally for me?
Because I don't have any mods.
Like, I don't want to play with mods.
Not yet, at least.
Noita is very CPU intensive, more than GPU.
It makes a lot of sense.
I mean, it's simulating all these pixels at the same time.
Not much graphical fidelity, right?
Chad was predicting you dying to that, mate.
Ah, shit.
Okay.
It will actually install every mod ever created for Noita.
I knew it.
That's why I try not to do that.
No, I don't want every single mod.
Ever created for Noita at the same time.
Okay, it's just gonna do a quick restart.
Got it.
It was so predictable.
Damn.
Okay, I definitely need to see the mod again to see what happened exactly in that moment.
Because now I'm curious, you know?
Is there something that I missed?
Apparently, everyone else was like, here, it's coming, it's coming.
And I'm like, going about my business?
I didn't see anything coming at all until it happened.
I'm so sad I died this time, though, because I had so much money.
You know?
Maybe I got a little greedy there.
I shouldn't have gone into the fungal place.
That place is nuts.
I don't know why I did that.
I didn't have that great weapons, so I shouldn't have done it.
You want to hold 20 potatoes?
Nice.
Wait, so how many did you bet?
Isn't that quite a little amount?
I feel like people were talking like they had potatoes in the thousands.
Oh, you mean it as if you lost a lot.
And you only won a little bit, maybe.
Yeah, 20 potatoes is nothing.
You have 32,000...
35,000!
Damn.
I just realized, I don't have any potatoes.
No, wait, that's not true.
I have infinite.
It actually says infinite potatoes for me.
Beat that.
Maybe that's cheating.
Oh man, this was sorely needed.
I've been missing Noita, man.
I felt so bad Thursday, Friday and yesterday.
Like, I was feeling sick.
But I was so sick that I couldn't really play, you know?
Like, at least not at the same time and enjoy it.
So I was really looking forward to this.
I'm so happy I actually got healthy.
I'm still feeling a little bit weird, but I'm mostly healthy now, so that's nice.
This was so needed.
Loved this game so much.
It's heartbreaking to die in this game at times.
But the best part is, you just want to get right up on that horse again, you know?
Like, it doesn't leave you broken.
Glad you're feeling better?
Thanks.
Yeah, same.
I was waiting for Noita this Friday, but now I know why.
Me too!
I was also waiting for it.
Yeah.
Every Noita run is winnable, which is why this game is so good.
I guess technically, yeah.
I mean, if you have enough skill, you could want...
You could technically win with just the wand you start with.
With a starter wand.
You know, like, two spark bolts.
You could technically do it, I guess.
If you dodge enough and you do this and that.
I mean, I guess so.
I mean, and then, of course, you're gonna find upgrades and all that, but...
Aye, of course.
Do you have any idea when you're gonna stop playing this game?
Hmm.
I don't know yet.
I mean, when I don't have fun anymore.
I don't know when that will be.
Or not when I don't have fun anymore.
More like when I feel like playing something new.
You know?
I can imagine coming back in the future to this game.
Here and there, randomly.
Just to play a little bit more.
Fill out more of the map, you know.
Try to go for a nice run.
I'm probably not gonna do everything I can in this game this time around.
I'm gonna come back to it later at some point, but for now, I'm still playing it.
Yeah.
Is this about skill and more about knowledge?
Yeah, that's the exact impression I also get.
The fact that you guys knew something was gonna happen with that guy and I didn't.
That was the difference, right?
So when I get that knowledge, that would not happen in the future.
In best case scenario, I mean.
You think there'll be a stream tomorrow?
Oh, I don't know about that.
I have a lot of stuff to do tomorrow.
Probably not.
But ASAP.
I will of course put it on Discord when I have a stream planned.
And I don't know if you guys know this, but there's actually a schedule you can click on.
On Twitch, on my channel.
And you can see, when I plan a stream, usually 24 hours in advance, but it could be less.
I actually put it on that schedule.
I don't know if there's anything you guys can see at all, or if it's something that you can get notified about, I don't know.
But I put it there just in case.
As well as on Discord.
Anyway guys, I'm gonna raid someone.
Is there someone we should raid?
Do you guys have suggestions?
Is someone online right now?
That is very raidable.
In Noita, of course.
We're gonna raid Noita people.
Let's see here.
What do you guys say?
There's actually a nice UI for me where I can sort by category.
It's like the raiding screen for me.
The Saibatsu Corporation.
Let's raid Okinawa.
Okay, let's do that.
Here we go.
Alright guys, thank you so much for watching, subscribing, and just hanging out.
It's always a blast.
I hope you guys are having a wonderful Sunday, and in case I don't see you, good morning, good afternoon, good evening, and good night.
There it is.
Okay, have a good one.
Bye-bye.